Who's there?!
How dare you break into this house.
Do you know whose house this is?
Where's the key?
Under the tree pot.
Hands above your head.
And slowly turn around.
Hey, where are you going?!
Shit, this is all I got?
Not worth it at all.
Good thing no one caught me.
I don't think...
Sol saw my face.
Mom.
Joe, is that you, Joe?
Mom, I'm sorry.
Did I wake you up?
Joe, Joe...I'm hurt.
Mom, Mom, Mom!
Mom! Mom!
Joe, how's your Mom?
Joe.
So, what happened?
The doctor said she had a Pulmonary edema.
That's why it's hard for her to breathe.
But she's getting better now.
Pulmonary edema?
And how did it happen?
The doctor still needs a few days for thorough diagnosis
before we know what caused it.
Right now, we could only assume that it's something about her kidney.
I have a relative who has a problem with a kidney, also.
But what I wanna tell you is...
the medical equipments now have been improved.
Trust me, your Mom is going to be okay.
She'll be fine.
Thanks.
These past two years...
she had been working very hard for me.
And when I woke up and now she's like this,…
was it worth it?
Joe, listen...
No mothers in this world want their kid to die.
If you want to blame something,
blame the old karma.
Don't blame yourself.
Believe me.
When are you two gonna get passed all this terrible mess?
Don't overthink.
Hang on.
What's up?
Ming, again?
Okay, I'll hurry. Wait for me, okay?
What's wrong?
There's someone in my team is having a problem with Ming.
Excuse me, I need to clear this up. / Alright.
And today, you don't have to go to the office. Take care of your Mom.
Thank you. / See ya!
See you, see you.
This is for Joe's sake.
Since he repented
and moved to Korea, so I left him alone.
And what's this?
He's back and he's breaking into my house.
Watch your words.
The reason I went to Korea wasn't because I was afraid of you.
But I'd have missed Joe if I'd stayed.
And the important thing is...that is Joe's house.
Not yours.
It's our house.
Joe will be back.
Accept the truth.
You're trying to redeem yourself because you're the cause of his death.
He's not dead yet!
Hey, hey, hey, calm, calm, calm.
Ming, no.
Calm down. No!
Sol.
Just a thief breaking into Joe's house is bad enough.
Why would you two fight?
A thief? There's no thief, only your beloved bro here...
sneaking into my house and making things up.
I guess he missed Joe so much that he couldn't help it.
And why would I do that?
Sol.
And why did you go there?
When I got back to Thailand,
I missed him...
So I came over...
You sneaked in and got scared so you made this up.
See, Wut? I told you that we should clear all this on our own.
No need to tell him.
C'mon.
No matter what, Ming is the one who lives there now.
But...is there anything missing?
Little cash and some membership cards.
Maybe that thief wanted to steal credit cards or ATM cards?
But without a passcode,
he wouldn't be able to get the cash out. That's weird.
I think he's trying to get other valuable things.
But he saw me first.
Well, about this...
We need a professional to manage.
If this gets to the police,
the press will definitely get it.
And both of your names will be shown.
Things will even get out of hand.
My family knows a good and trustworthy private detector.
Good. Then, I'll leave it to you.
And you, give all the information as much as needed.
Check the CCTVs from every alley around the area.
I think some of the CCTVs must capture the thief.
I'm on it.
How are you doing, Mom?
I'm okay. So what is it, darling?
Well, we gotta wait for the diagnosis for a few days first.
If...if it's something really bad...
Mom!
Don't say that, Mom.
It might be just the lack of sleep.
I hope so.
And why do I have to stay here?
I actually can go home.
Mom, it's better for you to stay here.
You can take a rest, and people can come take care of you.
I can support you, Mom.
So don't you think about it.
You have to take lots of rest so you can recover soon.
Thanks, darling.
Excuse me.
I'm here to ask about the initial payment of my Mom's bill.
Oh, the initial payment includes the admission.
The X-ray, the doctor's treatment, dialysis and filtration.
The initial payment?
Yes, this is the initial payment.
You have to consult with the doctor first.
So we can conclude the medical bills.
Thank you.
Hello.
Hello, Joy.
Yes, who's this?
It's Joe.
Wut's stuntman.
Well, I'm interested in the tryout to be Tong's stand-in.
Er, I'm sorry, Joe.
Tong has already got his stand-in.
Alright.
Cut.
Okay, I'm really okay with this, Tong.
This won't do.
From the back, you can see that it's not even close.
But this is the closest stand-in that we could find.
The closest isn't still enough.
And the one that's identical is not here anymore.
Joy.
Oh, Joe.
Who's that?
The stuntman whom I told you about.
The one I wanted to cast as your stand-in.
Interesting.
Hey, you wanna finish this scene first?
Then, you go change first,
and play this scene for me.
Thank you.
Man, did he hear what I said?
I've never thought that in this life I gotta be his stand-in again.
Tong.
We've shot so many scenes.
If we're gonna change the stand-in right now, I think...
I'm the owner of this project.
If he can do it,
I'll do the reshoot.
Alright, up to you.
Ah, hey, ready to shoot. C'mon.
Everyone, are you ready? Ready?
The cast, are you ready?
Ready, and...
action!
Cut!
I think he's not so different from the other guy.
They're all the same.
Who told you that?
From behind, he looks exactly like Tong.
Ming, when did you get here?
If I were you, I would choose him as my stand-in without question.
If that's what my biggest fan said...
I would have to agree with that.
Here. This is the contract. / Yes.
Keep this.
We'll have a lunch break and then we'll continue in the afternoon.
I'm happy for you.
Thank you, Joy.
I'll do my best.
Thanks.
Excuse me.
Where are you going?
Stay.
How did you cast for Tong's stand-in?
Well, I used to play series for him.
So Joy asked me.
And who taught you all the moves?
I like watching Tong's movies.
So I remembered his moves.
Hey, Ming.
You know each other?
I used to shoot an ad with Mr. Ming.
Oh.
Tong.
I want to play in this movie.
Is it possible to write a role for me?
Really?
At first, I invited you, and you didn't even think about it.
I saw that scene earlier and I think it's interesting.
Of course, I'll have the screenwriter write a role for you.
And if this project...
has you in it, it will be so famous.
Hello. Hello.
Hello.
I'll leave this to you.
Don't let this get to the police.
If what Sol said was true,
that means the thief must be in a hurry.
And he didn't destroy any evidence.
Shit, I forgot.
I haven't moved anything.
Okay, tonight, I'll be there.
And tomorrow, you come to check again.
Huh? Tonight?
I can't let Ming go back to my house tonight.
What should I do?
What are you doing?
Er...well...
Well...
Oh, a crew asked me to ask Mr. Ming to a party.
A crew?
Which one? Why didn't I know about this?
Er...
Mr. Ming, we have something to do tonight.
It's alright.
They asked me to go. How could I say no?
Then, why don't we all go?
It's on me.
Yes, we all should go!
Cheers!
Mr. Ming.
Would you like to sit here? I'll arrange it for you.
Hey, Ming, come here. I've saved you a seat.
Excuse me.
Would you like me to make you a drink?
It's alright. I'll have the waiter make it for me.
You can go sit with the crew.
I'm an extra who was in the scene with you today.
Would you like something?
I'll make a drink for you.
It's alright. I don't want to drink tonight.
You don't like a crowded place, right?
Me too.
How about we find a quiet place to talk?
It's alright.
C'mon, just for fun.
It's alright. I think...
Come here.
Excuse me.
Ming, why did you bring him here?
Mr. Ming would like me to entertain you guys.
Please, let me make your drinks.
This is mine.
Here, Mr. Ming.
Mr. Ming doesn't drink.
Thanks.
Just a bit.
Oh.
This is my job.
C'mon, let's clink the glasses.
One. Two. Three.
Ah, c'mon, c'mon.
Cheers!
Oh, you've drunk all of that, c'mon.
Let me pour it for you.
Cheers! Bottoms up! Bottoms up!
Wow.
C'mon, let this be the night!
Do you want anything else?
Oh, Mr. Ming. Let me pour more for you.
Bottoms up!
Mr. Ming, cheers!
C'mon, one more.
Cheers!
You're not drinking anymore.
No.
Are you going home now? /I'm gonna get going now.
Oh, okay.
I'll call my wife to pick me up.
Goodbye, Joy, goodbye.
Yes.
Safe travels.
This is still a fun night!
Ming, are you okay?
I'm okay.
Are you sure?
Er, yes, babe?
Oh, I'm still at the party now.
C'mon, let me pour you some more.
Please.
Let's clink the glasses, Mr. Ming.
Haven't I told you...
that Mr. Ming shouldn't be drinking this much?
I'm sorry.
I just wanted Mr. Ming to relax.
If he's like this, let's take him to his condo.
But I can't carry him alone.
You come here and help me first, and I'll give you a ride home.
Secretary Jim, I have somewhere to go, I gotta...
Stop it right there, this is your responsibility.
Mr. Ming, I'm sorry.
Alright.
One. Two. Three.
We're almost there, Mr. Ming.
Easy, easy.
Just a bit more, Mr. Ming.
Be careful.
Hey, hey, Mr. Ming!
Are you alright, Mr. Joe?
Mr. Joe!
Mr. Ming!
Joe.
Joe?
Er...Mr. Ming...well...
Joe.
Mr. Ming! Mr. Ming!
Er, I'm gonna get going now.
Secretary Jim!
Secretary Jim! Hey! Wait!
Joe.
Mr. Ming!
I miss you.
I miss you so much.
Joe.
The one Ming misses,
no matter which Joe is,
is not you.
Just go back and finish your plan.
Joe.
I miss you so much.
Don't be stupid.
Open your eyes.
The only one he loves is Tong.
Are you sure that the last time you came in, it wasn't like this?
I saw with my own eyes that only that shelf was destroyed.
That means the thief must have come in here last night.
He wanted to destroy the evidence to make us confused.
It seems like he knew that we're gonna come here today.
But I still have one more concern.
What is that?
The door has no sign of force entry.
Or maybe the thief had a modern technology tool...
or he might have a spare key.
But in the meantime, I'll check every little corner thoroughly.
If you have any more questions, please call me.
Excuse me.
The only one who knows where the key is...
Is there anything, Mr. Ming?
No.
Can you reach Joe yet?
He didn't answer any of the calls.
I don't know if this was about last night...
What about last night?
Nothing, Mr. Ming.
I'll hurry and reach Joe as soon as possible.
Excuse me, Doctor.
As far as we can see, the patient has no seizure nor cancer.
But the patient has septicemia which was from her kidneys not functioning.
This is an incurable disease.
But it's not deadly.
The patient must have dialysis every week.
And she'll have a normal life.
At our hospital, we have the department for that.
If you'd like her to do it here,
you can notify the staff at the counter.
If there's nothing else, please excuse me.
Thank you.
Sol, let me ask you this.
Why don't you go back and continue your career in Korea?
The industry here is too small for you.
At first, I thought about coming home just to rest.
But when there was a Joe's situation involved,
I thought about extending my stay.
So I'm finding stuff to do out of boredom.
Okay, if you'd like to make music here,
I have an actor for you.
I'd like you to have him in your new music video.
The new stunt of yours named Joe?
Okay, he might not look like the old Joe.
But I don't know why...
When I see him, I always think of Joe.
No one is like Joe.
No one.
Wut, Joe would like to talk to you.
Hey, I have something to talk to him too.
Let him in.
Wut, hello.
Joe, this is Sol. You might have already known him.
Of course, he's famous.
Sol is looking for a cast for his new music video.
So I think you should try the casting for his new video.
Oh, yes.
I don't think so.
Normally, I only use international celebs or the well-knowns.
Well, would you like for him to try first?
Joe, spin, let him see you.
So?
Just like I said?
I'll check if there's something suitable for him.
I'm not promising.
Thank you.
I have a doctor's appointment. Excuse me.
Okay.
Safe travels, see ya later, Sol.
So, do you have anything to talk to me?
Yes.
Well, my Mom's result is out.
My mom has a kidney failure.
She might have to do the dialysis for the rest of her life.
I get it now. So that's why you...
chose to be Tong's stand-in, right?
Oh, you know already?
Joe, I told you before, right?
If you have something, come to talk to me about it first.
I just didn't want to bother you.
I'm sorry.
Hey, it's okay. I'm not bothered.
And right now, I have some savings.
I'll let you borrow it first while you're waiting for your payment.
It's alright, Wut. Thank you very much.
I can't accept that.
Actually, I'm here just to tell you about Tong's movie.
If you have any work that I could do...
Don't worry, don't worry.
I'll try to push you as far as I can to make you be in Sol's new music video.
And in the meantime, if you have any troubles,
you must accept my help, alright?
Thank you so much, Wut.
No need to thank me anymore. Oh, and one more thing...
working with Tong, you must be careful.
Seriously, Tong is an asshole.
You can't trust him.
Alright.
Yeah, that's good.
If there's nothing else, excuse me.
See ya.
Goodbye.
Oh.
Easy, Mom.
Joe, I wanna go home.
Mom, the thing is the result came back already.
Mom...
I've asked the nurse already.
So you know...
Mmm.
There are so many diseases.
Why do I have to have the one that costs so much money.
It's alright, Mom.
I'm okay, darling.
Just knowing that you woke up and now you have a good job,
I'm not worried anymore. I can go see your Dad happily.
Mom, don't say that.
It's not deadly.
Joe.
The only thing I feel guilty about...
is being your trouble.
I'm old.
I want you to save up the money for yourself.
No need to cure me.
How can I not cure you?
Are you gonna leave me alone like this?
And the reason you're like this because you worked too much...
in order to find the money to cure me.
And how can I not cure you now?
I'm sorry, darling.
It's alright, Mom.
Why would you say sorry to me?
I've told you, from now on, I'll be the one who takes care of you.
Thank you so much, Son.
And have you eaten anything?
I have.
Take a lot of rest, Mom.
Alright.
Hello, is this Tong's movie accounting team?
I happen to have the urgent need for money.
Is it possible to have the money earlier than dated?
Joe's mom has a kidney failure. She's got no insurance.
And the minumum cost of the dialysis is 20,000 baht a month.
This doesn't include other expenses, Mr. Ming.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. / Are you alright?
I'm okay. I'm in a blur.
Can I talk to you?
Yes.
Why didn't you tell me about your Mom when we were in the meeting?
Well... / Well, what? You can just tell me.
I think that you don't seem to like me.
So I didn't know why I'd tell you about it.
Why?
Do you think I'll make fun of you?
No.
I'm just scared that if you knew about my Mom's condition,
you would unwillingly have me in your video.
And why would I do that?
Because you're a good person.
Am I right?
I don't dislike you.
I just don't like that you...
that you're like a guy I used to know.
Mr. Joe, right?
If it was Joe...
he wouldn't tell me about his Mom's condition as well.
He's very humble.
He would choose to put himself in trouble.
When he was banned,
he never thought about coming to me.
You're a good person.
I think he didn't want to drag you into his trouble.
How much?
What do you mean?
Your Mom's medical bill.
I'll lend you the money, and when you have the money,
you can just pay me back.
It's alright, thank you very much.
Well, I don't want to bother you,
and one more thing, we just met.
But I don't feel like that.
You're a good guy, Mr. Sol.
I don't want to drag you into my trouble.
Just you listening to my story,
I really appreciate that.
You're so much like him.
But, I got a job coming.
I'll see you soon.
See me?
Well, my music video.
I choose you, and you can't say no.
Thank you.
Hello, Mr. Ming.
I have something to talk to you.
Come see me at my condo.
I'm busy today.
I'll talk to you later.
Block him.
Are you going home?
Get in. I'll give you a ride.
Mr. Ming, you've given me a ride home.
What else do you want from me?
It's too much already.
That night, were you the one who got me home?
Yes, I went there with Secretary Jim.
I meant, were you the one who tucked me into bed?
Yes, I saw that you were very drunk.
I didn't know what to do, so I headed home after that.
Did I do anything to you that night?
I was in a blur too.
I couldn't remember it.
Mr. Ming!
What are you doing?
I just want to recall
why I did this to you.
Mr. Ming! Mr. Ming!
What exactly do you want from me?
Hey, Mr. Ming!
I'm asking you, what do you want from me?
Do you want to be famous?
Huh?
What role do you wanna play? What project do you wanna be in?
I can give you all of that if you just come stay with me.
And why are you helping me?
You're like one person that I used to know.
So I want you to be his stand-in.
You're so much like him.
Like Tong?
Tong.
Why didn't you choose me?
A stand-in, right? A stand-in should be able to play anything...
I'll leave it to you?
Don't be so full of yourself.
You're just a stand-in.
Mr. Ming!
Get out!
Get out of my house now!
I always get what I want.
Mr. Ming, if you're lonely...
I have so many people with good profiles...
He's so similar.
And, how much was it?
Three million Baht.
Oh, the first payment...
is the admission.
The X-ray, the doctor's treatment,
dialysis and filtration.
This is an incurable disease.
The patient must have dialysis every week.
And she'll have a normal life.
Do you want to be famous?
What role do you wanna play? What project do you wanna be in?
I can give you all of that if you just come stay with me.
Joe.
Can you forget everything and go back to the way we were?
Ming, it's not your fault, it's mine.
I didn't know that I was just a stand-in.
Don't worry.
I've told you, from now on, I'll be the one who takes care of you.
Five million Baht and a house for my Mom.
In exchange for one year of my life.
Do you think you're that worthy?
And what do you think?
Get used to it.
A year from now, there'll be more to come.