[You did well today, too. Pat, pat.]
I'm voluntarily single.
[Plastic Love]
Is it lonely being single?
Not at all.
As long as I have my cellphone, I can meet my ideal type anytime, anywhere.
This is my privilege in a single app.
[Pietro]
Where are you?
[Sky Ocean]
I've arrived. I'm inside.
[Pietro]
Oh, I'm also right at the front.
[Sky Ocean]
I'm wearing a sky blue shirt.
Hello, I'm Pietro.
Hello, I'm Sky Ocean.
You're much cuter in person.
Yes, I hear that a lot.
What would you like to eat?
I'm okay with anything.
Excuse me?
Here you go.
Cheers!
Do you meet a lot of people using the app?
Yes, well...
How many?
I cannot tell you a number, really. I tend to meet people for different purposes.
Someone to eat with, watch movies with, and drink coffee with.
Like this.
What about dating then?
If you date someone, you can do all that with one person.
I don't do that. I don't believe in it.
I see.
You should take that.
Oh, no. Please eat. Sure.
Have some of this too.
Thank you.
- You should eat, too.
- Oh, sure.
[Today, A Glass of Wine]
I enjoyed the meal.
Yes, I did, too.
Well, then...
Excuse me!
How about a cup of coffee? There's a nice café near here.
We only agreed to eat today.
That's right.
Can we meet again?
I had fun today.
Sure.
I have set a rule.
I don't meet the same person twice.
Everything should be simple.
[Block user]
Team Leader Seo, why aren't you picking up your phone?
Is it because the proposal was dropped?
Come on, Writer. I'm fine.
It's no big deal.
My single life was perfect. I could not ask for more.
Until that punk tackled it.
[Seo Yi Jun, Team Leader]
[Played by Cho Hyun Min]
[Jeong Ha Ram, Team Worker]
[Played by Cho Han Gyeol]
[Are you looking for true love?]
[Love Mate - Movie]
[What is "Single Heaven"?]
As I mentioned earlier, "Single Heaven"
emphasizes that both love and dating are illusory
and tries to differentiate itself from existing dating programs.
I'm certain that viewers no longer believe in the sweetness of love.
Because in today's society, love is not an absolute emotion.
It's an unnecessary, uncomfortable,
and even unpleasant emotion.
So rather than wrapping it up nicely and making it misleading,
I want to focus on reality
and ruthlessly show that love and dating are all curses.
Instead of wasting precious time with useless emotional consumption,
I think the right choice is to enjoy a fabulous and glamorous "single life."
[Distrust... Knows nothing about dating? Loser? ]
This concludes the presentation of my new project proposal, "Single Heaven."
Please feel free to ask me any questions.
Yes.
Well, I can't relate to this proposal at all.
First, I'll introduce myself.
I'm Jeong Ha Ram, a new Planning and Production Team member.
The reason I can't relate to Team Leader Seo Yi Jun's proposal is...
The reason is?
Because I believe in love.
Sure, you might not believe in love. However...
I feel like "Single Heaven" was written up by a relationship virgin.
- A relationship virgin?
- Yes.
A loser who doesn't know how to date or has never dated before.
That prick.
What's your basis for thinking that?
First of all, it's too emotional. It's not objective. How should I put this?
Like the negative emotions of someone who has been hurt in a relationship?
They also keep denying love,
but I don't think they're familiar with the concept.
They're just being biased
and insisting their opinion is right.
I was momentarily reminded of these words.
If you're going to trash something/someone, at least be well-informed.
- On top of that...
It also seems like they deliberately expressed abhorrence to hide their desire.
Well, that's another trait of a relationship virgin.
Don't just recklessly misinterpret the intention.
Anyway, I don't like this proposal for this reason.
Let me ask you one last question.
What do you think love is, Team Leader?
[No to Love! Yes to being Single!]
Love is...
a useless emotion.
All right. I knew you would say that. That's all.
Let's not be hung up on it.
Indifference is the answer.
A loser who doesn't know how to date or has never dated before.
Gosh. A relationship virgin?
How absurd.
[Planning and Production Team]
Do these not bloom?
Drink a lot of water.
Hey! What are you doing right now?
Oh, you're here. The plants looked too dry.
They'll get bacterial soft rot and die!
What are you doing at my seat without permission?
Oh, really?
I'm sorry. I didn't know.
Enough. Go back to your seat.
Seriously.
Team Leader... Team Leader.
Team Leader!
Don't they flower?
I've been observing them because I'm curious.
Yeah, they don't. Mind your own business.
Team Leader, you can't stand me because of yesterday, right?
I don't hold grudges like that.
What about this?
It's for you to get over your grudge.
Your face can't hide it well.
I don't drink coffee in the morning.
That's why I prepared one more.
An apple a day keeps the doctor away, right? Right.
An apple is perfect for an apology.
(Apple and apology are the same word in Korean.)
I apologize for my excessive honesty yesterday.
What? What?
Hang in there today!
That prick must still have a conscience.
Seeing how he gave us bribes.
Do you call these bribes?
You know, I thought about it all night.
Don't misunderstand and hear me out.
What the prick said yesterday...
I think it's valid to an extent.
Pardon?
I'm also really angry and upset our proposal got rejected.
We worked really hard on it.
But at times like this,
you need to see the facts more objectively.
What facts?
I don't want to admit it, but he's right.
- I'm a dating loser.
- Sorry?
You know my situation. I got divorced not too long ago.
Love? Dating?
I shiver just at the thought of it.
That's why I couldn't be objective.
That's why I reflected upon myself.
That's why... this mess happened.
I'm in the middle of deeply reflecting and repenting.
What in the world are you saying?
Hey, are you also one or not?
Am I what?
Let's both make confessions here and now.
That we are losers in dating.
What are you saying?
I'm not a relationship virgin.
Rest your hand on your heart and tell me honestly.
I know you only have flings through dating apps.
What's wrong with that?
Sure.
Team Leader Seo,
when was your most recent relationship?
That was...
See? You don't remember, do you?
In that regard, let's do it.
No, we must!
Do what exactly?
Love sensibility training.
L-Love training?
Take this opportunity to meet someone.
Let's recover our lost sensibilities.
This is the only way to save our proposal.
Don't you think the method is too peculiar?
Just trust and follow me for now.
Team Leader Seo,
when was your most recent relationship?
When was it again?
What is the use of recalling that?
Love sensibility? That's ridiculous.
I like things as they are now.
Team Leader!
Excuse me.
Team Leader. Team Leader!
What the heck?
Wow. What a coincidence.
I'm so glad to see you.
Is it fate and not a coincidence?
It's hot. Go somewhere else.
There are so many empty seats.
Why? Isn't it cozy between workplace seonbae and hubae?
You must not be happy to see me at all.
Do I have a reason to be?
Wow. You sure know how to hold grudges.
Are you still upset?
Let's go quietly.
Daebak. Sure, sure.
I'll do as you say.
Without permission, once again!
What do you call a fish wearing a bowtie?
Sofishticated!
What did the ocean say to the beach?
Nothing, it just waved.
[What is "Single Heaven"? Proposal Objective]
Team Leader Seo. A drink after work?
I can't.
Let's go. Let's go!
Drink? Let's go.
My work life was under duress because of that punk.
Team Leader Seo, lighten up!
I'll give you a chance to throw a punch at the newbie later.
Really?
Hey, you're here.
- Okay, Okay.
- Hello. Hello.
Writer, can you switch seats with me?
Sure.
I'm sorry, but can you switch seats with me?
Thank you.
Honestly...
Gosh.
Come on, that's enough.
We're not playing musical chairs. Round and round...
Hey, D&D.
Let's drink and die. Fill your glasses and raise them.
One shot! Let's have fun!
Cheers!
Eat up.
Team Leader.
Do you know what a newbie like me wants the most at work?
I'm not interested. Don't talk to me.
What is it? I'm curious.
A seonbae's affection.
Generous love for his hubae.
Do you want affection?
Hey, does someone who longs for affection
screw his Team Leader over like that?
Hey, Team Leader Seo is too kind.
If it were me, I would have slapped both of your cheeks.
Relationship virgin? Loser?
Hey, take this chance to officially apologize to your team leader.
- Wait, Manager.
- Hey, it's okay.
A hubae should show affection first,
for his seonbae to adore him.
All right!
I'll officially apologize to you.
In return, please grant me one wish.
No. J-Just sit down.
Hey, Team Leader Seo.
Accept his apology and grant him a wish!
Okay?
Team Leader...
I won't call you a loser in dating ever again.
You're absolutely not a relationship virgin.
So please don't hate me too much.
I'm sorry.
Can I tell you my wish now?
Let's do a love shot.
What?
What the heck?
Love shot.
Love shot. Love shot.
It's my wish.
The two of you...
You guys should be our official team couple starting today.
- Happy?
- Hey.
One glass is disappointing. I'm overflowing with affection.
Show us.
Show us. Show us.
Fine. Let's do another glass.
Sounds good.
Let's do it with soju.
Team Leader!
Aigo, are you all right?
Go away.
- How can I just leave you here?
- Just leave me alone and go.
Gosh.
What do you want from me?
Why can't you leave me alone?
Since it's your fault.
My fault?
Tell me. What is my fault?
That you're shaking up my heart.
What nonsense are you spewing? You're drunk, are you?
No. I fell in love with you...
at first sight.
What?
♫ At first, I couldn't help my fluttering heart ♫
♫ I can't help but look at you to my heart's content ♫
Hey.
Even if I seem like a pushover to you,
you should know when to stop.
I provoked you intentionally. Shock treatment.
Since you don't believe in love, Team Leader.
So? You fell for me. So what?
I want to...
date you.
What?
You're definitely drunk and out of your senses.
I'm very serious right now.
- What is 8 times 9?
- 72. See? I'm fine, right?
Dream on.
Why?
Why should I date you out of all the people?
Do you think you're special?
I'm tall.
I'm reliable.
And most importantly, I'm handsome.
I might look like this, but I'm top-notch when it comes to blind dating.
That's what you think. I don't think so.
Which aspect of me?
That ridiculous shock therapy
and a confession out of the blue.
You probably thought it was the perfect plan.
But right now, you're being rude.
I am super offended right now.
I'm sorry, but you better give up on your feelings.
Gosh.
Oh, wait!
Aren't you curious... why I like you?
Not one bit.
Really?
As you already know, I don't date.
I don't like to. Relationships are too bothersome.
Getting caught up in mixed emotions is the worst.
Then why do you meet people through apps?
You're so tenacious. How did you know?
I vaguely heard it from the writer.
Yes. I meet people through apps.
That's simpler and nice. Why?
Since there aren't expectations or a need for unnecessary emotions.
Not because you're afraid?
Let me say one thing.
You're... not my type. Period.
Hold on!
I'll make sure... you date me.
"He fell for me"?
That's absurd.
He'll lose interest on his own.
[Title: Runaway Penguin]
This crazy psycho-
That hits the spot.
Yes. I meet people through apps.
That's simpler and nice. Why?
Since there aren't expectations or a need for unnecessary emotions.
I'll install them all.
What's this?
No thanks. I don't get hangovers.
Pardon?
Didn't we clear things up last night?
Things like this won't work on me.
Team Leader, are you still drunk?
Wasn't it you?
What makes you so sure?
Was this really not you?
Give it to me if you won't drink it. Good.
I was suffering from a hangover anyway.
No matter how busy you are,
you should take care of your looks.
Looks are more important to me than you think.
I don't just like anyone.
You're crazy.
I'll really drink this.
[Quiche Mignon]
Yes, Writer.
Yes, I'm inside.
Yes, all right. Okay.
Team Leader! Did you enjoy your lunch?
Have a seat here.
I've already ordered everything.
What are you doing right now?
What are you scheming?
I changed the route a bit.
Now that I have confessed to you,
I will pursue you head-on.
Wow. Sudden brake.
Stop fooling around and change lanes.
What's with you two?
Writer, what do you do if you get bitten by a rabid dog?
There's no cure for that.
Let's go over there.
Have a seat here.
Assistant Manager! Here. Over here!
- Hurry, hurry, hurry.
- What's this?
I ordered everything already. Did you enjoy your lunch?
It was okay.
Have this. Have this!
Gosh, the stress.
What is it? Huh?
It's nothing. Don't worry about it.
Anyway, when will you start the training?
I have to do it, right?
If you trust me completely.
I'll think about it some more.
Writer, what would you like to drink?
An iced vanilla latte for me.
- Okay.
- 130 cm?
It doesn't look like it.
But you're 180 cm tall.
That's a 50 cm difference...
Ajeossi! Ajeossi, stop!
Team Leader. Look at this, another coincidence!
I'm worried you might fall.
Hurting the same spot twice is unfair.
I'll give you three seconds to take your hands off.
One, two, three!
♫ I can't wait to know, Baby ♫
♫ I want to know how you feel ♫
Did you know?
Playing hard to get is your charm.
Passing through.
♫ At first, I couldn't help my fluttering heart ♫
♫ I can't help but look at you to my heart's content ♫
I should ride the subway from now on.
I couldn't even imagine at the time...
that misfortune could also become destiny.
Manager. Did you look at the draft?
Yes, I got it. It looks fun! Good luck!
Thanks.
He only meets people through apps?
Then I'll find you, no matter what.
Hey. Aren't you working?
Aigo, so strict.
I was taking a short break.
What would you need a break for?
I brought the actors snacks and set them up.
I got the draft and delivered it to you.
I helped the props team organize the props.
I helped carry the lights for the lighting team.
What else did I do?
Newbies are supposed to gain experience by doing this and that.
And don't just wait for orders. You should look for things to do.
Take a look at the snack table.
A lot of people took things.
Alright, I understand.
Could you two help me out a bit?
Sure, how can we help you?
Please fill in for the test shots.
Excuse me? Isn't it the newlywed concept today?
Oh, good.
Let's use this chance to take official couple photos for you guys.
Manager...
I am sorry, Writer, but I can't do it.
The female model is really tall.
She's about your height.
- That's still a bit overwhelming for me-
- No!
We'll do it.
This is part of our job.
Isn't that right, Team Leader?
Of course, of course!
The team leader should set a good example for his workers.
That's right. Please do me the favor, Team Leader Seo.
Don't think too hard. Let's go.
Letting personal feelings influence work is a bit pathetic.
Let's go.
Can you put your legs on his?
My l-legs?
Good, that's it.
Okay! Just like that.
What are you doing?
This is a pose from the draft.
You checked it yourself.
Let's just get it over with quickly.
That depends on you.
This is the draft.
Ha Ram, very good.
Can you put your arm around his waist?
Yes, just like that. Good, good!
Okay, okay. I'm going in.
Why are they so good?
You know we're supposed to kiss at the end, right?
Can I do it for real?
Oh, my! What's wrong with him?
Team Leader! Team Leader!
[Photographs and Outings]
He's making me worry.
Team Leader.
Is he dead?
What did you do to me?
That's what I want to ask you.
Explain what just happened.
Do you think I did something to you?
I just checked to see if you were breathing or not
since you lied there like a corpse with no sign of getting up.
How did the shoot go?
The actors came and started shooting.
What? Hey, let's h-hurry and go!
Take responsibility.
Responsibility for what?
This.
It was a mistake. It didn't mean anything.
Even if it was a mistake, it still happened.
Okay, relax.
Let's calm down your breathing.
Let's purify it calmly.
Team Leader Seo, I'm sending you the photos from earlier.
Daebak!
I must be crazy.
Hello.
- Team Leader Seo.
- Yes, Manager!
I showed your photos to the CEO for fun.
- Ph-Photos?
- He loved them.
The CEO said we should use them for the cover story of next month's online newsletter.
Y-Yesterday's photos...
- Yes, yes.
- Are you talking about-
A work seonbae-hubae concept, full of love,
along with an interview.
What if you guys started dating for real?
This has been very wrong from the start...
This can't be...
[Single Heaven]
Team Leader, it's good to see you. It's a good morning.
You and I are strangers from now on.
Don't talk to me or even look at me. Just...
Just treat me like I'm invisible.
Is this because of what happened yesterday?
Not just yesterday! Gosh.
My life is breaking down because of you.
- Breaking down?
- Yes.
My proposal is on hold because of you,
the manager teases me at every chance, and I ride the subway instead of the bus.
You bother me and make me uncomfortable.
It's all because of you.
You're not allowed within three meters of me from now on.
What if I decline?
You'll pay dearly if you keep looking down on me.
How? How will I pay dearly?
Y-You just will.
- What are you doing?
- Just one second.
Just look at me for a second.
That's a relief.
There's no problem.
Wh-With what?
I searched online and learned there are people sensitive to light.
They could have seizures, and they could even faint in severe cases.
Light sensitivity or something...
I wondered if that was why you fainted yesterday.
Whether I have a seizure or faint is my problem.
Who made it your business?
Well, my face is... pretty radiant.
I'll feel bad if you faint again because of me.
I want to always stay by your side.
Your heart is pounding again, like yesterday.
It's because you raise my blood pressure.
I thought it was because I stirred your heart.
What a letdown.
Don't even appear in front of me.
He's even more like a penguin today. How cute.
Here you go.
Thanks.
I heard you fainted while posing for the poster shoot.
I couldn't sleep a wink because I was worried.
It's not a big deal. I just...
It's not because you were stressed
from my insistent training requests, is it?
No way.
Should we... just give up on Single Heaven?
Pardon? A-All of a sudden?
I call myself a writer, but I only say foolish things.
And I'm not of any help.
It was all wrong from the very beginning.
What kind of dating program when there's no romantic sensibility?
That's unnecessary guilt. I'll do the training.
Really?
I'll think of it as field research.
So don't worry or feel overwhelmed.
Sorry.
Didn't you tell me you'd ride the subway from now on?
How is that any of your concern?
You're the one who appeared in front of me this time.
It's not my fault the three-meter restriction was violated.
Did I say anything?
Anyhow, when did you get on?
I didn't see you at the bus stop.
I thought you might yell at me again if you saw me at the stop,
so I got on at the stop before.
You can say it was out of respect for you.
I even got on earlier so I wouldn't run into you.
But this must be fate.
Why are you staying still today?
It's better than falling over and embarrassing myself.
Are you all right?
Do you want to have dinner with me?
Why should I?
Eating alone gets lonely. Well, it is like that for me.
I don't know.
I'm better off finding someone through an app.
Gosh, it's so hard to go on a date with you.
Would it be possible to meet through an app?
Which app do you use? Tinder? Xexy?
Which is it?
I'm leaving.
So? You fell for me. So what?
I want to...
date you.
Gosh! I was in a daze again!
I should look for a training target.
[Plastic Love]
Let's get some work done.
Antarctica?
The South Pole?
But his profile picture is a polar bear.
The contradiction is unique.
Keep him for now.
[It's a match!]
Daebak!
Nice to meet you, Sky Ocean.
Yes, nice to meet you.
It's an honor to have matched with you.
That's stretching it.
This is like a dream for me.
Could you show me a photo of your face if that's okay?
My face?
Not because I'm judging by looks. I just want to feel your vibe.
Oh, I uphold a mysterious concept.
I don't like mysterious concepts.
What's your ideal type?
Someone like a polar bear.
That's exactly me!
What about you?
Someone like a penguin.
I have a question.
What do you think true love is?
Whoa, what a profound question.
It was written on your profile.
A welcoming heart.
Whenever, wherever, without any change.
Do you want to meet?
Really?
Wow! I'm finally going on a date!
I was... oddly attracted to him.
[Seoul Forest]
I got the feeling that he's... Single Heaven's savior.
[Gallery Garden]
Have you arrived yet?
Yes, I'm wearing a beige-colored jacket.
Sky Ocean.
Nice to meet you.
What the... Why did you come here?
It can't be, right?
Is this... also part of your plan?
You're the one who "liked" me first.
My only sin was installing the app.
Well, that's...
Even so! How could you pretend not to know me?
I just wanted to go on a date with you,
but you only meet people through apps, so there was only one way.
I looked for you all over the place, installing all kinds of apps.
I didn't even imagine.
You might not have imagined it,
but it seems like you looked forward to it.
I bought it because I didn't want to look shabby.
Nothing more...
Since it turned out this way, let's go on a date.
The weather's nice too.
You think I came here to play around like you?
You probably came here to train your love sensibility.
How deep are you trying to dig?
I'll teach you some love sensibility, so date me.
Are you really going to leave?
Team Leader!
Let me ask you one thing. Why do you like me?
What about me do you like?
You said you weren't curious. This is out of nowhere.
I just suddenly became curious.
How about... a drink?
Fine. Let's go.
Wait! We need to clink glasses.
I'm quite sweet, aren't I?
Yes.
Many people got drunk on my sweetness and asked me out.
Can't you feel how sweet I am?
Tell me the reason now.
The reason I like you is because...
you tied my shoelaces.
Shoelaces? When did I ever?
Don't you remember?
Oh, daebak.
Excuse me, Mr. Jeong Ha Ram?
Yes?
[Jeong Ha Ram]
"Fighting" today.
Excuse me.
Yes.
You're quite a handful.
If you end up in our department, you should come prepared.
We don't tolerate clumsiness.
They won't come undone now.
Are you nervous?
Yes. I'm really nervous.
If you're that nervous, you might fail the interview.
- Fighting!
- Fighting.
I was very touched back then.
It was a trivial moment, but my heart was fluttering.
It's as if I saw the light,
that moment... that encounter...
That's a delusion.
It's usually like that when a person falls for someone.
Team Leader, can I ask you a question?
What is it?
Are relationships really a bother for you?
Will you not like anyone for the rest of your life?
It's obvious. I won't.
In my opinion, I think you want to, but you can't.
I'm right, aren't I?
Don't go assuming things.
Just tell me honestly.
Why should I tell you?
Since I did the same.
I used to like and trust... someone with all my heart.
But I was betrayed, to my dismay.
It's embarrassing, but I was dumped over text.
He just sent a message, and it was over.
[Seo Yi Jun, let's break up.]
[Don't you have any manners?]
[You cheated and went off the grid. And now, you're breaking up with me like this?]
Rather than being sad, I was just... really embarrassed.
Were my feelings that insignificant? I felt a sense of shame.
It's just a common break-up repertoire.
Maybe I'm unusual, but it was hard to recover from that.
That's when I came to the conclusion...
to not like anyone...
and have unnecessary feelings for someone.
Your feelings...
aren't insignificant.
They're very precious.
Don't blame yourself...
for your partner's idiocy and ignorance.
So... clear away those clouds
and try to see the sunlight.
It turns out, our team leader
is actually quite fragile.
I shouldn't have told you.
Let's drink up.
Let's part ways here.
Already? Let's just have one more drink.
Enough. That's it for today.
It's me.
How is this you?
It's reliable.
As if.
Team Leader. Do you want to try this?
I've never done this before.
I'll teach you. Take this opportunity.
I'm putting the money in.
Okay.
Team Leader! Why would you press the button already?
I told you I didn't know how to do this.
Gosh, I don't understand.
I could do this with my eyes closed.
Hey, then you try it.
I can't believe it.
What will you do if I get one?
What do you mean?
Will you bet your entire fortune and hand?
What will you do if you can't get it?
I'll grant you a wish.
Deal.
Okay.
Okay, feeling good.
Good location.
Nice!
Nice! Success!
Let me collect your hand first.
Hey, we just did this for fun. What's wrong with you?
This is mine now.
What the heck? Let go while I'm being nice.
Let's go take photos for evidence now.
Wait, wait!
[The special day in four cuts]
- Hey, hey...
- Hurry, hurry, hurry!
This is the one.
No, no...
- Pass.
- Wait. Do I have to wear this?
Yes, you must.
This one.
Something's missing.
There... amazing! Look in the mirror.
Wow.
I want to make this into a keychain and cherish it.
You promised.
This photo will be your last photo with me.
All right. I'll take a video then.
What?
How do I look? Is this your style?
Stop wasting time. Let's hurry up.
Let's go.
[Story Edition]
Team Leader, look at the camera. Relax your face.
- Pose properly.
- Ah, seriously!
Hey! We're not close enough to pose like this!
Just do your thing.
All right. I'm going to press the button then.
Okay.
Team Leader, thank you...
for going on a date with me today.
Me, too... thank you.
What?
I was able to become more honest thanks to you.
Then should we... become more honest?
[Photo Print]
Are we going to do this here?
Your lips taste like soju.
You're getting more drunk on them, huh?
Absolutely.
How does it feel to be honest?
It feels good.
What happened last night feels like a dream.
Thankfully... it wasn't a nightmare.
What are you doing?
I thought you might be embarrassed,
so I was going to leave quietly. Good morning.
Eat before you leave.
Do you want to eat ramen?
We had ramen... last night.
(Term used as euphemism for "sexual activity")
Good, right?
Yes.
I always cured my hangover with spicy foods. This isn't bad.
Not the hamburger.
To be honest... I have feelings for you.
But they're not a 100%.
It was pretty sudden...
I need more time to think about it.
To be honest, this is what I expected.
But I still feel happy.
All right. I'll wait for you.
You got it all over your face.
Good boy.
What should we do today?
I don't know.
It's the weekend.
♫ Right now, this moment with you and me ♫
What should we do?
Cheers.
♫ I think about you first thing in the morning ♫
♫ You grow in my heart ♫
♫ Just looking at your lovely smile makes me happy ♫
Are you busy?
I asked if you were busy.
The call is not going through. Please leave a message...
Hey!
- Do you know Assistant Manager Park?
- Why aren't you picking up?
Assistant Manager Park will... Let's go.
What's with him all of a sudden?
He didn't say a word to me all day
and treated me as if I was invisible.
Ah, I am upset!
Was I too harsh on him all this time?
He's not doing this to tease me like a kid, is he?
Hey, why are you ignoring me?
[Ha Ram]
Is this too straightforward?
Did I do something to upset you?
Why do I get such a bad feeling?
It's probably nothing.
Whoa, hold on! Hold on!
You feel restless, don't you?
Me?
Your eyes give it away.
Now you know how I felt all this time, right?
I'm not sure.
You asked for some time to think.
I didn't want to disturb you.
Gosh! I'm so glad to talk to you after a whole day of evasion.
- It was just one day.
- What do you mean by "just"?
Every minute, every second with you is like an hour.
I'm done thinking.
Already?
There wasn't much to think about.
I'm so excited and nervous... about what you'll say.
Let's talk during lunch.
Just tell me now. Don't make me restless again.
Wait.
[Quiche Mignon]
I'll get straight to the point.
Let's be date mates.
Date mates?
Yeah. Rather than starting to date right away,
let's decide after getting to know each other better.
How should I put this...
It's somewhere between flirting and dating.
When we've already crossed the line?
I know it's out of the ordinary,
but...
I'm unfamiliar and cautious with these emotions.
I'm also scared I might mess up if I rush into it.
- Because...
- Because?
I'm a relationship virgin, like you said.
And I am fragile when it comes to emotions.
I really want to do well.
And I also want to get to know you more.
Then let's do it, Date Mate.
Really? Thanks.
How about we set a duration of a month?
Sounds good.
But... what if we both don't think we're right for each other?
It's better than hating each other and regretting it later, right?
For now, let's set some rules.
- Rules?
- Yes.
Next month...
Let's keep it a secret at work.
Excessive touching is off limits.
♫ I can't wait to know, Baby ♫
♫ I want to know how you feel ♫
♫ Your heart is fluttering like mine ♫
♫ I can't wait to know, Baby ♫
♫ There's never enough time for me to love you ♫
♫ I can catch a star for you if that's what you want ♫
♫ If you're afraid of the dark, I'll make it bright like your smile ♫
♫ No matter how hard I try ♫
♫ I can't imagine not having you by my side ♫
♫ Honestly, looking at you ♫
♫ I think I know how you feel ♫
♫ This feeling I can't hide, it's love ♫
♫ I can hear it louder than the ticking clock ♫
♫ My heart, please hold back ♫
♫ Even if I pretend I don't like you ♫
♫ A smile naturally appears when I look at you ♫
♫ I can't wait to know, Baby ♫
♫ I want to know how you feel ♫
♫ Your heart is fluttering like mine ♫
This was tiring, but it lifted my mood.
You like it more because you're with me, right?
Do you need to confirm it every time to feel satisfied?
Team Leader, I want to set a rule, too.
What is it?
Let's choose pet names for each other and speak comfortably.
You've never called my name even once.
You always call me "hey" or "you."
Well, that's...
By chance, it's not because you don't know my name, right?
As if I didn't know your name?
Then call my name now.
What's the big deal?
Ha Ram.
I can't hear you.
Ha Ram. Jeong Ha Ram.
I'm touched.
I want to set that voice as my ringtone.
It takes little to move you.
You can drop the honorifics.
But you... not at work.
All right, Yi Jun Hyeong.
("Older brother", but is also often used in close friendships or relationships)
But "hyeong" sounds a bit cringe.
But you say it so naturally.
Of course. I've been calling you that in my heart.
It's so you.
Did you know?
Polar bears and penguins can never meet.
That's why this moment is so unbelievable to me.
Wow...
This feels so nice.
[Single Heaven]
[Single Heaven Proposal]
[Empty Recycle Bin]
Before I knew it, a small change reflected in me.
It was a bit unfamiliar, but I decided to trust it.
I'd like to change the Single Heaven proposal.
Team Leader Seo, what?
You want to change the direction of the proposal after all this time?
What's your reason?
I think we were a bit too hasty with Single Heaven.
I don't think that's the only reason.
You can't fool these eyes.
To be honest, I'm seeing someone.
Daebak! Have you succeeded with the training?
- Is that why you changed your mind?
- I can't say you're wrong...
Anyway, I'll send you the draft soon.
I'm sorry for the inconvenience.
Of course, it's what you want. I am with you.
Seeing you full of confidence eases my heart.
You must have found the answer, huh?
I'm not sure yet, but I'll do my best.
Let's pick ourselves back up and do our best.
Gosh! I'm honestly a bit envious of you.
Gosh, why be envious?
What's with the tumbler?
What else? It's a couple's item.
Couple's item?
What's with that reaction? It's disappointing.
We agreed not to be like this at work.
I'm doing this because we're at work.
- Seriously, you're...
- Why?
Stop being so reckless.
I know you like it, but you're just being shy.
I'll just use this at home.
I knew you would be like this. So I prepared one more thing.
What? What is it? Spill it!
I ordered couple t-shirts too.
What? Couple t-shirt?
I'm sorry.
You were so cute just now.
Cancel it this instant!
I don't want to.
Doing this without consulting me is unfair.
Team Leader Seo, "A couple t-shirt"? What was that? Are you dating someone?
No, I was just working on the proposal.
You're not buying couple t-shirts with the newbie, are you?
- Pardon?
- I'm kidding. Look at this.
The newsletter cover draft is out. Daebak! Look at those eyes.
Hearts are shooting out. Pop, pop!
Come to the rooftop garden immediately.
Why did you react like that if you like it?
We agreed to keep this a secret. You're not cooperating.
I'll let the tumbler slide, so cancel the couple t-shirts.
They're already being shipped.
What?
Should I return them?
You don't even mean that. Oh, right.
Here.
Hyeong, you came out nice.
Especially your gaze.
What about my gaze?
It's out of the ordinary. It seems like you've fallen for me.
You're right. To be honest, you shook my heart a bit at the time.
Is that why you fainted?
No.
I fainted while holding my breath because I didn't want to breathe the same air as you.
I guess I'll just have to believe that.
Oh, let's take a picture.
What picture?
To commemorate our first couple item.
Aren't you tired of taking pictures with me?
As if. Don't be shy and get close to me.
The couple item.
Lift the photo so it's more visible.
Like this?
Yes.
Make pretty faces. I'm taking it.
One, two, three!
What the... What are you two doing here?
Oh, I was showing him the cover.
Team Leader Seo, something is going on here, isn't it?
You two seem to be hanging out a lot recently.
No way. You know we're not on good terms.
You're really suspicious.
Exactly. You used to argue all the time.
Did you know it has already been ten days since we became date mates?
Already?
Time really flies, doesn't it?
You're right. Time really flies.
How is it so far?
Not so bad, except for the couple t-shirt.
What about you?
That's my answer.
I heard you were preparing a new proposal.
Wow, you're so well-informed.
So what are you planning?
It's a secret.
Tell me. I'm curious.
So you can trash it again?
Maybe.
I might be more critical if it sucks.
I'll have to do well to avoid your criticism.
But did I make you feel that insulted back then?
Yes. It was the most humiliating day ever since I came into the company.
I apologize. Please forgive me.
Let's toast to that.
- What a beautiful weather.
- Yeah.
[True love is having a welcoming heart, whenever, wherever, without any change]
What the... Didn't you go home?
I did. I did, but... you wouldn't leave my mind.
You didn't eat dinner yet, right?
It's a hassle.
Do you mean that I'm a hassle, or that it's a hassle for me?
Both?
So aren't you happy to see me?
I'm very happy.
With words only? I want you to express yourself.
Oh, right.
Look at this.
Okay, I believe you. It's so funny.
Oh? This!
[True love is having a welcoming heart, whenever, wherever, without any change]
Isn't this what I said?
So what?
I'll need to collect royalty fees.
What are you saying?
Let me join the proposal. I'll give you my share.
You're kidding, right?
Working late with the person I like is on my bucket list.
I'm merciless. You're out as soon as you lose focus.
Of course, I'm just going to work. What are you imagining?
I'm just saying.
Hurry and eat so we can get to work.
Are you serious?
I'll help you. It's too much to do alone.
But if I suck, you can mercilessly criticize me, too. Deal?
Deal.
Did you choose a title for your new proposal?
It's too early. I don't even have a draft yet.
Really?
It's always easier for me when I begin with a title.
Just like...
a sprout grows from a seed, ideas sprout from my head.
I see. It would be nice to begin with a title.
Bucket list?
Jeong Ha Ram.
Jeong Ha Ram. Don't sleep here. Go home.
Are you done?
I still have a little more left.
Let me know when you're done. I'll take you home.
I can take a taxi home.
Go home before the last bus.
Then I'll just take the taxi with you to your house.
My house?
There you go again with your dirty thoughts.
Anyway, just wake me up.
I worked too hard today, so I'm out of it.
Hand.
Hand!
Why?
Let's hold hands and sleep.
I can hear your heart really well.
Should we just take the day off tomorrow?
I'm suddenly wide awake.
What will we do instead of sleeping?
What you kept thinking about.
I did not think anything like that.
Then what I kept thinking about.
Let's go to sleep. We'll really be late tomorrow.
All right.
Good night, Hyeong.
[What is true love?]
[Objective]
Is it midnight already?
Jeong Ha Ram.
What's that?
Happy birthday.
How did you know?
I was too indifferent, wasn't I?
You should have told me in advance.
My heart feels like it's going to explode.
Make a wish before it explodes.
- Happy birthday!
- Thanks.
So... what did you wish for?
For your proposal to be accepted.
You made that up to cheer me up, didn't you?
Tell me! What did you wish for?
No. Wishes aren't meant to be shared.
Then let's clean up here. It's late.
No gift?
Wasn't the event enough? What more do you want?
Our secret late nights at work continued, and in the end,
the new proposal was complete.
[True Love]
♫ I can't help but look at you to my heart's content ♫
♫ When you call me, I get flustered for no reason and blush right away ♫
Next, Team Leader Seo will present his new proposal.
Applause.
I present my new proposal.
The title is called "True Love."
We ambitiously prepared a healing dating program
that heals the wounds of breakups through new people and finds true love.
Team Leader Seo, you did really well!
We finally passed!
Leave the rest up to me.
I will pour my soul into writing the script.
- Fighting.
- I'll put my trust in you.
Shall we have a celebratory party later? It will be my treat.
I-I'm sorry, but I have plans later.
Is it a date with the person you're seeing?
Yes.
Oh, well, it can't be helped. I'll back off today.
- Let's set a date soon.
- Sure.
Do you at least want to get a drink with me?
I also have plans.
Yes? Today must not be the day.
Anyway, great job, everyone.
- You did well, too.
- Thank you.
Hey, what are you up to?
Thanks.
What did I do? You did all the work.
Gosh, you constantly stayed by my side.
That's not easy.
I'm honored, Team Leader Seo.
By the way, where are we going later?
It's a surprise. You can look forward to it.
A surprise? What is it?
It's a secret.
Aigo, you did so well.
Unveiling your body isn't the surprise, is it?
I rented this entire place... for you.
Here?
I'm joking. I asked the director for a favor.
Hand.
Hey, wait, wait!
Give me a second.
One... two...
Surprise!
This is for you.
What do you think?
The mood is so nice.
I always wanted to come here... with the person I like.
What is my next surprise?
His name is Yun Do Kyeong.
He's a former swimmer, currently modeling under the stage name DK.
[Name: Yun Do Kyeong]
I just tossed them the "True Love" proposal. I simply tossed it. But...
They caught it. They reached out to us, saying they wanted to do it.
What do you all think?
Team Leader Seo, what's with your expression? Don't you like him?
With his looks, he'll be... a huge help with viewer ratings.
I agree with you, Manager.
I see star potential.
I'd like to proceed. From what his agency says,
they also have a strong intention to support him.
And they said that he's willing to do anything we ask.
Let's take the easy road. The easy road.
Let's think about it a bit more.
Sure. The proposer's opinion is most important.
Please decide as soon as possible and give us a positive response.
My ex-boyfriend who made me miserable.
He showed up in front of me out of the blue.
Why now...
Yun Do Kyeong.
Something is fishy.
[D-Day]
Hyeong.
Is something wrong?
No, it's nothing like that.
You're lying.
You've had that expression ever since yesterday's meeting.
What's wrong with my expression?
It's full of stormy clouds.
I have become a bit sensitive preparing for the project.
There's so much to prepare.
Gosh, I already have a headache.
That's a relief then.
Don't worry. I'm like this every time.
No, you're not.
You're still wearing your ID badge after work.
Let me know if you're going through a hard time.
I don't like you stressing out alone.
Okay.
Have you made up your mind about DK?
We're interviewing him tomorrow, so I'll think about it then.
We don't really know DK, but the female staff are crazy about him.
He'll be really popular if he gains some publicity.
Sure.
Yeah.
[Cast Interview]
I hope it goes well.
He's here.
Nice to meet you. I'm DK.
It's sincerely an honor to meet you all.
This is Writer Jin Eun Seon.
And that's "True Love's" manager, Team Leader Seo Yi Jun.
What about "True Love" appealed to you?
Honestly, I was being materialistic at first.
I wanted to participate no matter what,
since it would be easier to become famous through a variety show.
But while reading the proposal,
something moved my heart.
At the same time, it made me feel regret and reflect on myself.
Regret and reflect?
Yes.
I took love lightly until now.
I took my partner's sincerity for granted and hurt them.
The moment I realized that,
our times together flashed by like a panorama.
I must have hurt them quite a bit.
They must have been hurt quite a bit.
I reached a conclusion amidst my misery.
I should learn what true love is.
Through this "True Love" project.
Isn't DK really great?
How does he have a great mentality along with his incredible looks?
Don't you think he could cause a real stir?
I'm not really sure.
Let's think about it a bit more.
Hyeong! How was DK?
The female staff were going crazy.
It was so-so.
Let's eat something really delicious for lunch.
My stomach is a bit upset.
I'd like to get some air.
I have medicine. Do you want some?
It's fine. It's not that bad.
I thought I had some, but I was mistaken.
Don't worry about me, and enjoy your lunch.
I'll stop by a pharmacy later and buy some.
I'm fine, though.
You had an upset stomach last time too.
I'm worried.
Don't worry.
[Seo Yi Jun, let's break up.]
[Don't you have any manners?]
Should I just tell him everything?
Yi Jun.
Do you know how long I've looked for you?
How have you been all this time?
You even became Team Leader. Congratulations, Seo Yi Jun.
What the hell are you doing?
Do you know that it has been three years since we saw each other?
These are your favorite lisianthus flowers.
- Have you seen Team Leader Seo?
- No, I haven't.
I don't need these.
Seo Yi Jun! Seo Yi Jun!
I really missed you.
After seeing your name on "True Love's" proposal, I kept thinking about you.
To be honest, I made this decision because of you.
Although I don't think you would believe me.
Funny. Who said I was casting you?
Yi Jun, I have something I must tell you.
- Can you make some time?
- Why should I?
Don't you know we're strangers now?
Your anger is understandable.
But it wasn't... all bad between us.
Do you have no shame?
How dare you show up in front of me?
I know I'm being shameless.
So I want to be different this time.
I'll wait... until you forgive me.
[Like the flower language of the lisianthus, with my eternal love, Do Kyeong]
[Feel better]
Why do I feel so conflicted?
I should just ignore him.
But it's hard to.
Can I go over to your place today?
I'm tired. Next time.
What?
What's so tiring?
What's gotten into you?
What about me?
It feels like you've been interrogating me for some time now.
It's getting on my nerves.
Then do something to get rid of that feeling.
Are you saying I'm hiding something from you?
Aren't you?
Hyeong, you go ahead.
- What about you?
- Don't worry about it.
- I'm really leaving.
- Go.
Writer!
Yes? What?
Could I talk to you for a moment?
All of a sudden? What's wrong?
Well...
- What?
- I'm seeing Team Leader Seo.
Are you the one Team Leader Seo was seeing?
Yes, with good feelings.
Oh my goodness.
Anyway, go on.
Well... we're not really in a relationship yet.
We're just date mates.
Date mates?
What's this about now?
We're seeing each other under the limit of one month.
But there's suddenly a problem.
What problem?
Someone interfered in the middle.
Interfered? Who?
My guess is...
Team Leader Seo's ex-boyfriend.
What is this? A soap opera?
But Team Leader Seo won't tell me anything.
I was going to feign ignorance and just overlook it, but...
I am concerned and anxious.
The biggest question is...
if I have the right to speak up.
Our date mate duration is coming to an end soon.
I don't want to ruin it all with a mistake.
So I have a lot on my mind.
Just be honest.
You call yourselves date mates, but you're basically in a relationship.
Am I wrong?
That's true.
You idiots.
You guys started with the wrong context.
If you like each other, just date. Why be date mates?
If it doesn't work out after the period is over,
could you just say your goodbyes?
Dear...
what do you think the biggest obstacle is when you like someone?
I'm not sure.
It's fear.
Go on and have an honest talk with Team Leader Seo.
Right now!
Okay.
Don't beat around the bush and get to the point.
What do you need to tell me?
I'm sorry.
I wanted to talk to you face to face.
Yi Jun, I was too disrespectful to you, wasn't I?
After all this time?
I guess, after all this time.
It's late, but could you forgive me?
What difference will that make?
I want to get along with you again.
You keep counting your eggs before they hatch.
That's not happening.
I know it's not easy.
And I know what I've done to you.
You did everything for me.
When I said I wanted to model,
you fed my vanity with shoes and clothes.
And since I was jobless and loafing around at home,
you introduced a part-time job to me and also managed my diet.
And... when I failed an audition,
you always cheered me on in case I lost self-esteem.
I remember every single thing you've done for me.
To be honest, you're the one who made me who I am today.
I'm really grateful for that... and sorry.
And you still did that?
You still made me feel that miserable?
I've forgotten all my memories with you.
- So I decline your trip down memory lane.
- Yi Jun...
You want to get along after appearing out of the blue?
Sure. It must be easy for you. But I...
Forget it. Let's stop here.
I'm really regretful.
Please let me repay everything you've done for me.
Cut the bullshit.
What do you want from me?
Is it because of the program?
Do you think I would... approach you with ulterior motives?
I just...
realized that there's no one else like you in the world.
If I could go back in time,
I would never do something so stupid.
- Please...
- Let go.
- I'm sorry.
- I said, let go.
Please give me one more chance.
I'll be good to you. Please!
Why isn't he picking up?
Please, damn it!
Hey, Yun Do Kyeong!
Let go of my hyeong.
Who are you to meddle?
Me?
Seo Yi Jun's lover.
Hey, Seo Yi Jun. Is he really your lover?
- That's enough, both of you.
- Is he, or isn't he?
Yun Do Kyeong. Why should I answer you?
Hey, Jeong Ha Ram. You're being discourteous.
Hyeong.
Both of you, leave. I can't deal with this.
I'm sorry that I put you through this.
I'll get going.
You should go, too.
Do you want me to leave in this situation?
[Today, A Glass of Wine]
Enjoy.
Why didn't you tell me?
That Yun Do Kyeong was bothering you.
It has nothing to do with you.
It has nothing to do with me?
Right.
It's my problem, so I was going to solve it myself.
This wouldn't have happened if you had been honest with me.
Is it because I'm your date mate?
Is that all I am to you, Hyeong?
You don't know how I feel, do you?
Being whipped around by my ex... was too pathetic.
So I hid it.
I was honestly going to properly end things with Yun Do Kyeong today.
But you appeared out of nowhere
and everything was messed up.
I've been extremely embarrassed to see you.
I realized something while looking at the two of you.
What?
I'm still... not ready to like anyone.
It's not anyone's fault. It's all my fault.
Honestly, I didn't tell you because a part of me doesn't trust you.
I was afraid I would become petty.
I am afraid that fear... won't be easy to overcome.
And I don't want you to get hurt because of me.
Let's just... end things here.
We became date mates...
because of my fear in the first place.
Let's stop being date mates.
Nothing makes sense.
It's tough to sort out my feelings... and it's tough for you, too.
Let's just end it here.
Team Leader Seo, did you make up your mind about DK?
Writer Jin is totally okay with him.
Yes.
- Let's cast DK.
- What?
He's a hot topic and the best choice in terms of strategy.
And above all, he has a strong will, so let's trust it.
- What are you doing?
- Jeong Ha Ram.
We're at work. What are you doing?
What are you thinking, trying to cast Yun Do Kyeong? Huh?
Do you want him to keep bothering you?
Being hung up on my feelings is bothersome and a burden.
I'm just going to go with the flow.
And Yun Do Kyeong is a candidate for casting.
He's literally the best.
I don't want to make things harder by overthinking.
The same goes for you.
Can you really do that?
Even to me?
For three years...
I met people through apps without any feelings.
Things were nice and comfortable then.
I'll go back to that.
So don't make me uncomfortable like this.
We should have... never started to begin with.
All right. Yun Do Kyeong is here to join us for "True Love."
Applause!
Welcome!
Thank you in advance. I'm Yun Do Kyeong.
Please take good care of him.
And we can't just go home on a day like this, right?
Let's go for a team dinner. Pack your things and follow me!
Yi Jun. Do you have a moment?
I heard what happened.
I got cast because you gave the okay.
Thanks.
Let's do our best.
You're the only one who looks out for me.
I just went along with the company.
Don't put unnecessary meaning to it.
And let's keep it professional from now on.
With all due respect.
You got it, Team Leader Seo.
I'm repeating myself, but
I don't have personal feelings for you at all.
Don't get on my nerves by bringing up the past.
How could I? We've known each other for years.
Please do.
Do Kyeong, let's go.
Anyway, let's grab dinner sometime.
I found a really nice place.
I forgot to give him the draft of our contract.
Go take it to DK. He's probably in the underground parking lot right now.
Me? You can tell his manager to come up.
He's not picking up. Go on.
Geez, seriously.
You always make me do these things.
Always making me do everything. What a hassle.
Such a bother.
Yes, CEO.
Of course. I introduced myself to everyone.
Oh, the friend who created the proposal?
What should I do? I've got him in the palm of my hand.
Please. He does everything I ask him to.
He's naive, like a fool.
It shouldn't be a problem if I just keep at it.
Yes.
Come on, CEO. It's a done deal, so quit worrying.
It's all thanks to you.
Don't.
Hyeong.
Let's just go back up.
Why?
Why are you turning a blind eye?
Aren't you angry that he manipulated you?
Just let it be.
Going up.
The door is closing.
I'm going crazy.
Why isn't he picking up?
What's going on with Team Leader Seo?
He's still not at work yet. Did he contact anyone?
Did no one hear from him?
Give him a call and see if he's okay.
This isn't like him.
I'm a relationship virgin, like you said.
And I am fragile.
Nothing makes sense.
It's tough to sort out my feelings... and it's tough for you, too.
Let's just end it here.
- Manager.
- Yes.
- I have to go off site.
- Sure, go ahead.
Go off site?
Hyeong! Yi Jun Hyeong!
What?
Why did you come? What about work?
Do you think work is the problem?
Where does it hurt?
Just... I'm just not in good condition.
It's nothing serious.
You're lying.
You're hurting here.
Meet with Yun Do Kyeong.
Meet him and curse him out or argue.
Don't hold back the pain, and don't avoid it.
Don't be afraid and pour out the feelings you stashed away.
Forget it.
Doing that won't change anything.
Why not?
Don't let him look down on you anymore.
And I...
I don't want you to close up again.
Expressing and receiving emotions is difficult for me, too.
Other people are the same.
We learn from the pain and all the while, we keep at it.
Running away isn't the answer, Hyeong.
I know it's not the answer.
But it's not the wrong answer either.
No.
It's wrong to me, and it's awful.
I can't watch the person I like struggle with the wrong answer.
If it's hard to do this alone, I'll stay beside you.
To be honest, I was confident.
But I couldn't figure out how.
I was at a loss.
Pretending you weren't the one...
and pushing you away...
I kept thinking of you
and remembered the times we spent together.
I'm awful, aren't I?
Yeah. You're awful.
You're really awful.
But I'm awful, too. For not understanding you.
Let's not be like this anymore.
Don't be nervous. Be honest.
All right?
I'll do my best.
Yi Jun, you're here.
Have a seat.
What's going on? You asked to see me first.
I was surprised you reached out to me first.
It made me happy, though.
Thinking you've opened up to me a bit.
What is it?
Is something wrong?
What's wrong?
Shit!
What the hell?
Hey, Seo Yi Jun!
Where did he go?
Where are you?
Do you feel relieved now?
Yeah. A lot.
I'm proud of you, Hyeong.
But why did you leave?
I didn't want to pressure you, so I left.
Thanks.
[Last day of being date mates]
Hyeong, why are you so quiet?
Did you hang up? Huh?
You know what tomorrow is, right?
What about tomorrow? Is it a special day?
Yes.
[Gallery Garden]
Yi Jun Hyeong!
You're...
It looks like you're completely head over heels for me.
Totally.
Man, I should have dressed like this sooner.
So...
what do we do now?
Let's end it here.
What?
Let's stop being date mates.
Let's date instead.
We should have done this from the start.
Thanks for being patient and enduring all this time.
What about you?
My answer is...
I was dating you from the get-go.
♫ At first, I couldn't help my fluttering heart ♫
♫ I can't help but look at you to my heart's content ♫
♫ When you call me, I get flustered for no reason and blush right away ♫
♫ I can hear it louder than the ticking clock ♫
♫ My heart, please hold back ♫
♫ Even if I pretend I don't like you ♫
♫ A smile naturally appears when I look at you ♫
♫ I can't wait to know, Baby ♫
♫ I want to know how you feel ♫
♫ Your heart is fluttering like mine ♫
♫ I can't wait to know, Baby ♫
♫ There's never enough time for me to love you ♫
♫ I can catch a star for you if that's what you want ♫
♫ If you're afraid of the dark, I'll make it bright like your smile ♫
♫ No matter how hard I try, I can't imagine not having you by my side ♫
♫ Honestly, looking at you, I think I know how you feel ♫
♫ This feeling I can't hide, it's love ♫
♫ I can hear it louder than the ticking clock ♫
♫ My heart, please hold back ♫
♫ Even if I pretend I don't like you, a smile naturally appears when I look at you ♫
♫ I can't wait to know, Baby ♫
♫ I want to know how you feel ♫
♫ Your heart is fluttering like mine ♫
♫ I can't wait to know, Baby ♫
♫ There's never enough time for me to love you ♫
How much longer? I'm hungry.
Just wait a bit longer.
What's today's menu?
Chicken and beer? Wait.
How much longer?
Just a bit longer. Not yet.
I can do this better.
Then you do it.
I'm good, right?
You're good.
Hyeong, I think it's done.
Let's have a taste.
- It's delicious.
- Is it?
Interestingly, the air date is the same as our 100-day anniversary.
You're right.
What's with this coincidence that doesn't feel like a coincidence?
It feels really strange, though.
Our 100-day anniversary or the program?
Both?
You hung in there.
You, too.
With words only?
It's starting. Hurry, hurry.
Cheers.
♫ I want to walk holding hands ♫
Here.
♫ I miss you no matter how much I see you ♫
♫ In your twinkling eyes ♫
Wow! Your name appeared! There, there, there!
Your name too! At the back.
Wow. Daebak. That's so cool.
I hope it does well.
"True Love" has finally begun. Along with my true love.
♫ I keep smiling ♫
Someone I'm always happy to see is right next to me.
[A healing romance for you, "True Love"]
[Are you looking for true love?]
[Love Mate - Movie]
♫ It's a happy day, right now, this moment with you and me ♫
♫ I think about you first thing in the morning ♫
♫ You grow in my heart ♫
♫ Just looking at your lovely smile makes me happy ♫
♫ I'm all right if I'm next to you ♫
♫ I love it when it's the two of us ♫
♫ How can I like you this much? ♫
♫ Happy, happy day ♫
♫ I keep smiling ♫
♫ At this time right now ♫
♫ Tell me, love, love, love ♫
♫ Good love, love, love ♫
♫ It's a happy day ♫
♫ Right now, this moment with you and me ♫
♫ Let it be just like today ♫
♫ Even if time passes, I want to treasure this moment ♫
♫ A smile spreads ♫
♫ Everywhere you touch ♫
♫ Everything is happy ♫
♫ Happy, happy day ♫