[PARK SEO HAM]
[PARK JAE CHAN]
[SEMANTIC ERROR]
The timing and the subtitles are brought to you by
the Wacko & Psycho
Does destiny begin with a coincidence or a choice?
In a series of coincidences and choices,
we may stumble on destiny some day.
Good, isn't it?
That is pure genius.
That destiny may be benign to you, or it may be the exact opposite.
You want a picture? You could have asked.
Should I stand here?
Go ahead. Take a picture.
This semester is coming to an end, and the next is drawing near. Where has destiny taken you? Or to whom?
What was that? Did he just ignore me?
Jaeyeong! Congratulations!
Or what destiny will you choose to make?
Congratulations on your graduation!
Quick! Let's take a picture!
Let's do ugly faces.
- Give me a break.
- Let's just do a normal picture.
- Shut up, dummy.
- Why aren't you picking up?
Hyeongtak! Come join us for the picture.
This is no time to party.
- What's wrong?
- Take a look.
What is it?
- Horrible design.
- This is not a joke.
You're in trouble.
Me?
Character…
- The Character Education Course?
- All freeloaders are getting an F.
Does that mean you won't graduate?
Give me that.
This presentation at Character Ed was insane.
[JUSTICE WILL BE DONE!]
[A LOT OF PEOPLE WON'T BE GRADUATING]
[THEY ALL DESERVE THAT.]
We have to learn from the wrongs of the past graduates
and strive to instill good character in the students of this university.
For that, what's most important is honesty and fairness.
First, I've never seen such a crappy PPT (Power Point) in my life.
My name is Chu Sangwoo, and thank you for listening.
Secondly, he took out all the names of the freeloaders.
Also,
Mr. Chu Sangwoo.
...when the professor asked if they really hadn't participated at all...
One said they were homesick.
One said their greataunt just passed away.
They have no conscience. And the next thing he said was historic.
Some people think it's okay because they're seniors.
That's unfair to the underclassmen, who have to do more work.
I second that.
Do you agree?
Anyway, those freeloaders deserved it.
[221 | SCIENCE HALL | COMPUTER SCIENCE CLASSROOM]
Yeah, I'm here.
I'll ask him to talk to the professor. Yeah.
Chu Sangwoo?
I heard he only wears plaid shirts.
I don't see him anywhere.
[Hello?]
[Please answer my text :(]
[I have to graduate. Please. I'm sorry.]
[We need to talk in person.]
He ignored it again.
Why is he being so difficult?
Yeah.
I might have to do another year.
Worry about yourself. Bye.
- Sangwoo!
- What?
We need to talk.
- Who are you?
- You know who I am.
You're Sangwoo, right?
- No, I'm not.
- I know you're Sangwoo.
I'm sure you're the guy.
- Sorry.
- Chu Sangwoo?
Hey, Sangwoo.
No?
Sangwoo.
What the…
Jaeyeong!
Oh, come on! Everyone is dressed the same!
Is this your department's dress code or something?
- This is driving me nuts.
- What are you talking about?
- Are you looking for Chu Sangwoo?
- Yeah.
- Is he in there?
- No.
He handed in his test a while ago and left.
Seriously?
But I came here twenty minutes ago.
[Freeloader 1: Did you leave out my name? My greataunt just died. How could you do that?]
[Freeloader 2: I got an F. You happy?]
[Freeloader 3: I'm not graduating, thanks to you. We need to talk.]
[FREELOADER 3]
They're so persistent.
Hey!
You're early.
We're doing the map design, right?
Yeah.
There's something I need to tell you.
I'm so sorry.
I just got a job offer and can't do the project anymore.
I'm really sorry! This came as a surprise.
And also, they want me to start tomorrow and come to their workshop.
That's a surprise. The plan is already set.
Instead, I'll introduce you to a few possible replacements.
I'll give you their portfolios… Oh!
You went to the exhibit. Did you like any of them?
- Do you know if this person would be available?
- What?
Jang Jaeyeong?
He is about to go study abroad in the US, so I don't think he can.
Did you like anyone else?
Well, that's a shame. Thank you for everything.
Oh… You, too.
But wait!
We're done?
Is there anything else?
Well, no. But I still feel sorry.
Then let me buy you dinner. Do you have the time?
It's okay.
All right.
Bye!
There goes Chu Sangwoo.
He's as cold as ice!
Computer engineering junior.
Top student for all three years.
He doesn't do any activities. He's not even in the group chat.
He's not in any clubs, either.
Is he from Mars or something?
I know. Doesn't it feel like ages since we talked to him?
I can't remember his voice.
Give up trying to look for him. He'll give you a splitting headache.
That makes me want to find him more.
You're kind of a freak yourself.
Yeah.
So much effort went into this drawing.
It's a waste of good talent.
Chu Sangwoo. Are you playing tag with me?
He's getting me riled up.
[DANGER]
[RESULTS]
[FIND THE PIRATE SHIP]
[GAME INFORMATION - TITLE, GENRE, MODES]
Do you know a Chu Sangwoo?
Oh, I think I've heard of him.
I heard Jaeyeong can't graduate because of him.
There's quite a story. Jaeyeong is doing everything to find the guy.
You don't know him? I heard he's quite infamous in the department.
How would I know? There are hundreds in our department.
- Really?
I don't know him.
Still. I heard he's notorious.
[CHU SANGWOO]
What is he going to do anyway?
Hi there.
The same thing again?
I'm Ryu Jihye. Computer Science.
I borrowed some change from you before. Don't you remember me?
You're... 800 won.
That's all you remember?
That's okay. We can still be friends.
There.
I don't have the change for that.
That's fine.
I'll pay you for the difference later.
Wait.
Is this you by any chance?
This kind of looks like you.
The hat is spot on.
[WANTED]
These posters are everywhere.
Chu Sangwoo. Age 21. Junior. Comp Sci major.
Recently back from the military service. No club activities.
We need to talk in person. Or you'll be in a lot of trouble.
No use blocking this number.
He did a background check on me?
I could call that number.
[WANTED]
[Block Number]
I think he blocked my number.
What did you expect?
If I were him, I would think you're a wacko and just avoid you.
I'm starving!
We check out one last place, and then I'm done.
And you'll help me with my graduation project.
Hey, I'd rather sleep in the streets. That place was smaller than a bathroom.
It's not the size that matters right now.
What about furniture?
I'm only staying for six months.
You're impossible.
You shouldn't have given away your old furniture.
- Choi Yuna.
- What?
- If I ever freeze to death on the street,
make sure to bury Sangwoo with me. So I can talk to him in the afterlife.
- Sure. And I'll be glad to bury you.
- Okay.
- Enough talk about that guy.
- Hello, there.
Okay?
Hey. What are you doing?
Hold on.
- "Notice. Student Jang Jaeyoung, your graduation has been canceled."
- What?
- Slow down.
- Let him drink. He wants to die young.
- What? Who wants to die young?
- Hey!
I'm sorry I'm late.
I thought you were happy that you got a job.
But now you just look tired.
You guys should stay in college as long as you can before you get jobs.
Oh, right. I heard you can't graduate. Sorry about that.
Was that a joke?
Don't be too sad. Be positive. You won't have much to do, anyway. It'll be chill.
Right.
You're good, so you can go study abroad whenever you want.
You can have all the fun before you go.
I second that.
Also, I happen to have a project I need you to fill in for.
Not happening.
Come on. The developer saw your work and really wants you.
Could you do a favor for your dear friend?
He does have a keen eye. A developer? Comp Sci?
There he goes again.
He's a bit uppity but really smart, too.
I heard he's top of his class.
- What's his name?
- Chu Sangwoo.
Chu Sangwoo?
Yeah.
He scares me.
Okay. When do I meet him?
[ACTION RUNNING GAME: VEGGIE MAN]
[CHU SANGWOO],
About the guy you talked about last time. He's available, so I told him where to meet you. Good luck with your meeting!
Why isn't he here? It's time.
He's late to the first meeting. I have a bad feeling about this.
♫ The moment I was wandering through the dark universe ♫
♫ Copy the sun, every day is bright ♫
♫ You got me stuck. You got me stuck ♫
♫ All right ♫
♫ Step into my heart and you'll become my world ♫
♫ Oh, you're a romantic devil ♫
Are you the designer?
Yeah.
You must be Chu Sangwoo.
You're late.
I didn't think you would be handsome.
Do you know my name?
Yes.
It doesn't ring a bell?
Does that matter?
Aren't you here to talk about the game?
I am. I'm here to talk about the game.
Let me take a look.
"Veggie Man..."
I heard you were a genius, so I expected more.
Disappointing.
Your character design and the storyline both suck.
There's nothing special about this.
Are you sure this will work?
Do you have any experience with mobile games?
None.
I'll find another designer.
Are you really going to bury him?
You know that was a joke.
Then?
I'm just going to size him up.
If I like him,
I'll play along for a bit.
­[ACTION GAME]
[VEGGIE MAN]
How do you like it?
You have a punctuality problem,
but you're a good designer.
That's a compliment, right?
Give me your number.
[FREELOADER 3]
No wonder why you didn't recognize me.
You already have my number.
What?
That can't be.
[GROUP LEADER]
We finally meet,
Sangwoo.
Thanks for ignoring my texts.
You're not here to discuss the game. Clearly, it's something else.
Not necessarily. Let's put an end to our conflict, and we can discuss the game, too.
Nice, no?
Well, I never had a conflict with you.
It's just you holding a grudge against me.
Take it easy. Don't hate me too much.
I'm not picking a fight with you. So, just chill.
You sneaked up on me, and I just cannot trust you.
I have nothing to say to you, and I'm leaving.
Maybe you forgot, but you reached out to me first.
I thought you liked my drawing.
I did.
But that was before I knew you were "Freeloader 3."
I won't be working with you, so don't text me.
What if I do?
It took me a lot of work to find you.
I won't let go of you just yet.
There is still room for negotiation.
Just say that you're sorry for stalling my graduation.
Say it. Then I might consider your offer.
I have to fix two errors here.
One. I'm not the reason why you didn't graduate.
It's because you screwed up your GPA.
Two. I'm not sorry for anything.
If I have to say it accurately, you "failed" to graduate.
Hey.
I see you're a real wacko.
You're the wacko here.
Junior,
what do you hate most?
Senior.
- What color do you hate?
- Red...?
Why do you ask?
Any place you hate?
A 10-meter radius around you, so can you just—
Sangwoo.
I was going to let this one slide,
but I changed my mind.
You'd better brace yourself.
[LOOKING FOR A DESIGNER TO COLLABORATE ON A MOBILE GAME]
Are you looking for a designer?
Me, too.
Here. The change.
Have you been carrying this around just for me?
I wasn't sure when I would see you.
Can I have your number?
Why do you want my number?
We can text each other when we're bored.
We can also share information about designers.
Okay.
My arms hurt. My arms...They won't move.
Look at this. Look.
I can't move.
Good for you.
Out of the way!
- I can't move.
- This place isn't too small.
- Get out of the way.
- Come on.
- Move!
You're never nice to me.
This is for you.
Nice.
I thought you didn't like this place.
It's better than I expected.
There was another surprise, too.
What's that? Let me see.
Let's have lunch.
- Black bean noodles?
- Yes!
- Sweet and sour beef!
- And how about some Gaoliang (traditional Chinese wine)?
- ♪ Sounds perfect ♪
- You know your food and booze.
[MOVING: TODAY]
[BIG OCCASION FOR THE NEW SEMESTER: D-3]
Make the call and order.
- We'll pour the sauce on top.
- No! We'll keep it on the side.
[8:30 AM - WAKING UP]
[FIRST DAY OF SCHOOL]
[8:45 AM - MORNING WORKOUT]
[8:58 AM - BRUSHING TEETH]
[9:16 AM - GETTING READY FOR SCHOOL]
What's this?
[PUT YOUR BOXES AWAY, PLEASE! - From Unit 212]
[9:20 AM - GOING TO SCHOOL, DELAYED BY 2 MINUTES]
[9:25 AM - BUYING THE DRINK "BLACK HOLIC"]
This is weird.
[9:25 AM - BUYING THE DRINK "BLACK HOLIC" - X]
What is this guy up to anyway?
What do I do with all this?
[9:30 AM - GETTING THE THIRD WINDOW SEAT]
What a way to start the semester.
[9:30 AM - GETTING THE THIRD WINDOW SEAT - X]
I'm 30 minutes early. As scheduled.
- Whose stuff is this?
- Mine.
I didn't know you were in this class, too.
[APPLIED SOFTWARE ENGINEERING]
- Lee Seokhun.
- Here.
- Lee Hyeondong.
- Lee Hungi.
- Here.
Jang Jaeyeong.
Here.
Visual design major?
- Will you be okay in this class?
- Of course, Professor.
- I've always been interested in this field.
- Really?
Art merged with technology is the way of the future.
You're right about that. Let's move on.
- Choi Hyeonwoo.
- Here.
[CHU SANGWOO]
[BUG DETECTED]
[AGGRESSIVE RESPONSE]
[BUG RESOLVING ALGORITHM A]
[RETALIATION LAUNCHED]
[DANGER]
[4 STING COMBOS]
[WASTE OF TIME]
[AGGRESSIVE RESPONSE = WASTE OF TIME]
[BUG RESOLVING ALGORITHM B]
[IGNORING HIM]
[LOSS OF INTEREST]
[IGNORING HIM = SUCCESSFUL ELIMINATION]
[IGNORE HIM]
[HI, SANGWOO. THIS IS JIHYE FROM THE OTHER DAY. HAVE YOU FOUND A DESIGNER YET?]
Still no reply.
Just give it up.
Even a ransomware attack wouldn't crack him.
Are you saying I'm like a virus?
I'm just worried about you.
It's the infamous Chu Sangwoo you're after.
Have you ever seen him with any...
What?
What's up with those two?
What? You want to go on that plate? Okay.
Help yourself! I can tell you like broccoli.
You can have mine, too.
There.
Are they sharing their food?
They look pretty close.
Have some carrots, too.
Wait, Sangwoo.
Be a good boy and finish your food.
[CHARACTER EDUCATION GRADING RUBRIC]
[MANDATORY ATTENDANCE]
[FAKING ATTENDANCE WILL RESULT IN AN "F".]
Do I really have to be here every time?
What the heck?
Why do you keep dressing like that?
Just give me back the hat. I'll throw it away.
Red is a good color. It's eye-catching.
Exactly. That's the problem.
I'm seeing too much of it, and it's making me sick.
You're right. It's tough to take your eyes off it.
I can't tell if he's just calm all the time or is pretending to be.
It's tantalizing.
Is this about Chu Sangwoo?
Sangwoo hates the color red.
Also, he absolutely hates my guts.
Well, I also
hate your guts, Jaeyeong.
I hate you so much.
Gosh.
I could take his math class, too, if not for this class.
All that running for nothing. Too bad.
How do you know my class schedule?
Ta-da!
I thought you left it for me.
I see you got nothing better to do.
But this isn't working.
I like your patience.
Impressive.
[BLACK HOLIC]
Childish.
[FRENCH CONVERSATION]
[CONVERSATION TEST PAIRS]
[GROUP 1: JANG JAEYEONG - CHU SANGWOO]
Now, you're all sitting with your partners. Right?
Yes.
Professor.
I don't think my partner and I suit each other.
Can I get a new one?
I won't allow that. The whole point of this is to build teamwork.
Teamwork.
Okay.
Put your trust in me.
Bro will carry you.
[DRESSING IN RED]
Dressing in red... is not against the rules.
[JEOSURI MANSION]
Taking my favorite spot, is not against the rules.
Buying all the coffee, is not against the rules.
His very existence, is not against the rules.
The rules must be wrong.
Now I'm seeing things.
You scared me!
What is wrong with you?
Are you out of your mind?
Think about your neighbors.
I'm reporting you as a stalker.
For what?
For moving in next door to you?
That's not a crime.
You're lying. I don't buy it.
It doesn't matter if you believe it or not. It's what happened.
I moved in a few days ago, but I waited.
I didn't want to ruin the surprise for you.
I thought you were just an asshole. But you're a total psycho.
Thanks. I get that all the time.
Maybe you expected a dramatic reaction, but it's not a big deal when you do this.
That only makes me want to try even harder.
Give it another try, Senior Psycho.
Thanks for the encouragement, Junior Wacko.
Sangwoo! Sangwoo!
Are you okay? You don't look well.
I'm doing fine.
You have a nose bleed.
Oh no! What do I do?
Are you okay?
Look at that.
Who's that next to Sangwoo?
I think that's Ryu Jihye.
Ryu Jihye?
That's Ryu Jihye from Class B, right?
Yeah. I heard she's interested in Sangwoo. So, the rumor was true.
So, he's not that busy after all.
Why does he even drink this?
Oh, boy.
You want to play dirty, huh?
Why is he wearing his hat all the time?
Isn't it uncomfortable?
He's not bad-looking when he's not frowning.
Sangwoo! Sangwoo!
Falling asleep during the first week?
I'm sorry.
Like an art student, he carefully drew it on.
Bastard-like error.
Was that too much?
Hey. Are you crazy?
It's gone. I'm impressed.
Just quit already. Your childish pranks are not working.
It's funny. Your brows are twitching.
Why are you doing this to me? This won't help you graduate.
Graduate? The semester just started.
- Then what is—
- I have nothing against you.
I'm having a lot of fun this semester thanks to you.
What do you have to gain from pranking me?
Well... It just feels good.
Just tell me what you want from me. Stop fooling around.
What I want...
Take that off.
Your hat.
Are you kidding me? Do you think this is funny?
Relax. It's just a hat. And I only answered your question
You're wrong if you think your bullshit is working.
I'm not going to let this continue.
I'll take action myself.
That was cute.
Sangwoo is tougher than I thought. You practically got schooled.
Is what I'm saying.
And why the hat? You weren't going to take it, were you?
No way. I just wanted to take a good look at his angry face.
Wow.
That confirms you're a psycho maniac.
- Thanks for the compliment.
- Thank you for proving me right.
Stop it already.
What the…? Take a look at this.
What is it?
[PROUD ALUMNUS | MENTOR: KIM GYUTAE]
Isn't this that cheapskate who tried to exploit you?
He was the worst.
And they're hiring him as a mentor? Screw this school.
I suffered so much under him that I lost five kilograms (eleven pounds).
I actually liked you better when you were chubby.
Oh, come on!
Throw out these empty cans, or I'll kill you.
The coffee's taken care of.
Let me tie my shoes quickly. Just two seconds.
Excuse me.
And will you put this on my seat for me? It's tough to wake up early.
Hey!
Sometimes, you're even worse than me.
I know, right? You put your stuff in the wrong place.
Sangwoo!
See you in your dream.
Of course. I beat you.
I'm sitting next to you.
What's this? Is this the best you can do?
I'm not talking to you. I'm here for the class.
You took the time to think of this. I'll be a worthy adversary.
It flew out of my hand.
Will you pass it back to me?
Actually,
you can keep that.
He must be here somewhere.
Hear me out. During lunch, he sat with total strangers.
He went through that trouble just to avoid me.
Yeah, sure. We all know how much he hates you. Congratulations.
That's not the point here.
You know how strict he is with his routine.
He's going out of his way just because of me.
So what?
I just told you everything.
Hey, Jang Jaeyeong! What's your goal here?
My goal?
So what if he changed because of you?
Does that mean anything to you?
Do you want to be even crazier than you already are?
You're being unnecessarily logical today.
Just think about that.
Maybe you're picking on him because you actually like him.
I'm going.
Really?
[LOOKING FOR A DESIGNER FOR AN APP]
I'm so doing this.
[CLAIMED BY JANG JAEYEONG]
[THE ART OF RETALIATION]
I'll have to be more aggressive with him.
Take it easy. It's only the first week.
No nosebleed today?
You really got me worried that day.
Thank you for helping me back then.
All right. That means we're friends, right?
How does that mean we're friends?
We're not strangers anymore.
We'll be seeing each other more often anyway.
Sure. Okay.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Friends it is, then.
Hey, Jang Jaeyeong! What's your goal here?
So what if he changed because of you?
Does that mean anything to you?
My goal in this?
What a shame. I wish I could attend that class.
Hey. Can I ask you something?
Was that a question?
No. Just a rhetorical one that precedes the actual one.
Was your childhood nickname Sangchoo?
(T/N: Korean word for "lettuce")
How did you guess that?
Of course. I knew it.
Then, can I call you Sangchoo, too?
I don't really care.
Chu Sangchoo. It sounds cute.
"Lettuce"?
I hate lettuce.
You're Ji Hye, right? I'm Jang Jaeyeong.
Nice to meet you. I'm a fan of your work.
How do you know my name?
Let me just say I know everything about Sangwoo.
So, you two really are close.
- Yeah.
- No.
Now, come on. We practically spend every day together.
I have to go.
Okay. I hope you have a good class!
He's no fun, don't you agree?
And what class?
He's taking this class.
[PROUD ALUMNUS | MENTOR: KIM GYUTAE OF QUICKST GAMES]
"Quickst?"
Who is it? Tell me.
Are you guys dating or something?
She has nothing to do with me, so don't bother her.
I wasn't going to. Take it easy.
By the way, don't you know Quickst is total trash?
I don't care what you think.
Don't you know they always exploit people? Ask anybody on campus.
You and your friends got exploited because you're dumb.
Clearly, you have a problem.
No wonder you have no friends to warn you. You never listen to anyone, anyway.
What is it?
[CLAIMED BY JANG JAEYEONG]
This is better. It really catches the eye.
This might seem like nothing to you, but this game project is very important to me.
You're just pathetic and definitely not worth my time.
I don't need your advice. Go away.
It looks fun, doesn't it?
I bet you won't last three days.
Nope! Just wait, and I'll prove you wrong.
That was ferocious. You might break the board.
Are you not going after Sangwoo today?
Why that all of a sudden?
What? You're the one that's always talking about him.
Oh, right! Let me hook you up with a girl.
She's in your advanced programming class.
Advanced what?
Do you understand any of that?
Oh, you're withdrawing from that class next week. Right?
Why not take it all the way?
Are you nuts?
- You'll like her.
- No, thank you.
Come on.
Look, it's the Quickst guy.
Perfect timing.
That guy is so much worse when he's drunk. I don't want to see that.
Chu Sangwoo?
Whatever. Let's just drink.
You should have arranged everything before we came in.
Waiting is one of the things I hate the most.
You son of a gun.
With this hand, I'll teach you a lesson about being an actual adult.
When will you, kids, grow up?
I'll give you a good karate chop
Pow! Hand chop right there!
I'm sorry but I have to get going.
Chu Sangwoo, right? We still have a lot to discuss.
About that project we talked about,
I'll think about it when I get the documents.
Kids these days, like yourself,
simply don't understand how the world works.
I'm giving you an opportunity, and you should be thankful and have a roll-up-your-sleeves attitude.
That's what you need.
I think we should first discuss the issues regarding copyrights.
I'll reach out to you some time soon.
Have some courtesy and finish your drink.
How dare you! I offer you a drink and you refuse it?
- Show respect!
- It was a given.
So annoying.
Should we go to a different place?
Let's finish these and go.
I can drink this. But I don't want to.
I can see you're a bit antisocial, but this is not the right time or place.
Hands off. Hey, you. Are you disrespecting me?
You're laughing?
Clearly, you're too drunk.
Do that again and I'm calling the police.
You little punk.
Oops, that was a mistake. I'm sorry, it slipped out of my fingers.
- Mister.
- Yeah?
It's one thing to be drunk,
but if you do that again, I'll… put a hole right there.
What is this? Are you his backup or what?
- Yeah.
- No.
- What?
I'm with him.
Who are you?
Get off of me, asshole!
Hands off. Let go of this. I'm okay.
Did you just push me?
Shut your hole.
Let's go.
- You messed with the wrong person!
- Please, stop!
You see, I wasn't stalking you. I just saw you there, okay?
Yes, I know.
What if he called the police?
I'm a college student and he was drunk.
He wouldn't call the cops. Even though he is a wacko.
You don't seem worried at all.
Bye.
My bag.
My key was in there.
My phone is dead, too.
Hey, Sangwoo.
Can I use your laptop?
I don't know my friends' numbers. I'll message them on SNS.
Why don't you go back to the bar and see?
What if the crazy guy is still there?
I thought you weren't afraid of anything.
I'm not scared of him. It's just that—
I don't let anyone in my place.
Oh, come on. Ungrateful bastard.
No respect.
Ten minutes.
That will be it.
[JEOSURI MANSION]
This place suits your personality.
It's too organized. Really.
What's this?
You should get to it. You've got eight minutes left.
You're counting that?
I don't think I remember the password.
I'm not going to steal anything. I'm not a hacker.
Why don't you wash up, first? I can smell the alcohol from here.
I said I won't do anything weird.
But if you do that again, I'll…
put a hole right there.
I only get five attempts?
Hey, Chu Sangwoo! Do you know how to hack?
I shouldn't have let him in.
I shouldn't have let you drink.
That was some movie stuff back there.
- Come on!
- ♪ I am a lonely firefly ♪
(T/N: a famous Korean children's song)
[A NEW MESSAGE FROM ZZANG_JAE_O_O]
[HYUNGTAK, MY BAG AND MY KEY]
♪ I have no friends… ♪
- I've had enough!
- But he probably has a girlfriend.
♪ That pile of dog poop is my… ♪
You still couldn't find it?
I messaged them, but…
What are you looking at?
You look so much better without the cap.
You should stop wearing that.
That's none of your business.
If you're done, you should leave.
It's cold out there.
Just go.
You're being too harsh.
It's cold at night these days.
Do you want me to sit next to you and cough all day?
You're such a nuisance.
You let me in, so you should be a good host.
What's this?
There's a cut on your arm.
Are you hurt?
Not on me.
On you.
You scared me.
Where?
I don't see anything.
That hurts.
Take it easy, will you?
I haven't even put it on yet.
I know you hate me, but please go easy.
Then do it yourself.
Come on. How can I do it when I can't see it?
Fine. I'll keep quiet.
So... does that happen every time you drink?
I mean, you could have just played along with that asshole.
I would never do that.
Isn't that better, though, than making enemies?
I don't care about that.
I've met plenty of people like that. And I dealt with them.
You talk like a superhero.
You're the one acting like a villain all the time.
But still, thank you for today.
I still don't like you, but…
I appreciate what you did for me today.
That's more like you.
Jaeyeong! Come get your bag!
Come out and get your bag!
Uh...
I'll get going.
What the hell?
I must be going crazy.
Why do I keep thinking about him?
What the hell?
- Come on.
- Sangchoo! Over here.
Sangchoo?
Hi!
- Did you have lunch?
- Ryu Jihye?
What's up with those two?
Let me know if you like any of those. I'll give you the designer's number.
[ACTION GAME: VEGGIE MAN]
[CHU SANGWOO]
My baby's dying.
You save him.
It was going so well…
You're saying this happened because of me?
It was working fine yesterday until this happened.
That asshole must have stepped on it. I'm sure it was him. That son of a…
You'll help me, right?
What? You don't want to?
Then, you don't have to.
I guess it'll cost around 1,000,000 won if I take it to a computer repair shop.
Are you a pushover?
Give it here.
I think it's the D drive that's the problem.
That can't be the problem.
How do you know that's not the problem? How can you be so sure?
What are you going to do about my pictures?
Your computer was broken.
But why are the pictures gone? Why did you delete them?
They're gone. Just forget about them.
How can I just forget about them? Tell me.
You said you backed up everything important.
I also formatted your hard drive.
So what's the problem?
Still, you deleted everything. That's harsh.
Computers are like people in a way.
If they keep unnecessary things inside, they are bound to break down.
Or slow down at least.
Fine. You did well.
It's almost like you have a computer for a brain.
Why are you arguing with me again?
I'm not arguing with you.
I'm starting to understand how you process data.
You talk like I'm some kind of a machine.
It's something similar.
Let's go together.
Slow down. Wait up.
Oh, right. You're dropping that class.
Suyeong is looking for a designer. Interested?
- No.
- What?
You're not going to drop your class?
I'm not sure. Go away.
Then, help me with my project.
- Get lost.
- Damn it.
What is this? A new project?
No.  Just lately to loosen up my hand.
I thought you never drew people. Look at those strokes.
I can feel your passion for the subject.
Yeah.
I hate him, actually.
Whatever.
I'll tell Suyeong that you're out.
What do you hate the most?
You.
You're the one acting like a villain all the time.
So, how did your date go with your guy?
No, it was a total fiasco.
It was going so well before that senior jumped in.
What senior?
♫ The moment I was wandering through the dark universe ♫
♫ Copy the sun, every day is bright ♫
♫ You got me stuck. You got me stuck ♫
♫ All right. All right ♫
♫ All right ♫
♫ The colorful sky that spreads above the clouds ♫
♫ A beautiful star that pours out every night ♫
♫ You got me stuck. You got me stuck ♫
♫ All right. All right ♫
♫ All right ♫
♫ Knocking on my door ♫
Waiting for me?
♫ Step into my heart and you'll become my world ♫
What? Do I look stunning today?
♫ You've made a mess in my world ♫
♫ Oh, you're a romantic devil ♫
No red?
I'm impressed you noticed that already.
We're doing conversation practice today.
Put this down.
"Like this."
- We can do it on paper.
What is this, the Joseon Dynasty? Is this a secret conversation?
So,
have you thought of any possible topics?
Melodrama.
No way.
Let's go with "asking for directions."
That's lame as hell.
Remind me not to design a game with you.
How about two people who confess their love,
but find out they are half-brothers?
- What bullshit—
- The professor likes epic melodramas.
I'll make the script.
You can just pick out the lines you like.
You're going to write the script?
Yeah. I'm in the theater club. I direct sometimes, too.
What? You thought I would freeload again?
We have a perfectly good script here.
But your acting is just terrible.
We'll need more practice than I expected.
Isn't it just the pronunciation that needs to be correct?
Tell me the truth.
Have you ever dated anyone?
What does that have to do with this?
You're ruining the melodrama part completely.
Have you ever been in love with anyone?
If you're talking about emotional delusions, then, no.
Delusion?
Love is nothing but a delusion they propagate so people will reproduce.
It's unbelievable how narrow-minded you are.
If anything, I'm logical.
Then, what's your definition of dating?
It's just the phase that comes before marriage.
We could say it's like a beta test for software.
[BLACK HOLIC]
Just drink this.
I'm giving it to you because it's trash.
Why are you doing this?
What?
Maybe you changed your strategy, but fraternizing won't work, either.
Strategies are not my thing.
I always just do what I feel like doing.
See you.
What's with him?
The script looks okay, but…
what's he trying to pull?
Did he poison this?
No wonder he was so quiet.
He disturbs me even when he is quiet.
I didn't know he looked like this.
Sangwoo.
Can I open my eyes now?
I can't believe I did that to him.
Chu Sangwoo, what is wrong with you?
[FREELOADER 3]
[BASIC FRENCH PRONUNCIATION TIPS]
Watch this. It has some great tips on pronunciation.
What?
I thought he would be mad.
I will.
Use proper spacing.
Who do you think you are, King Sejong?
(T/N: the king who made the Korean alphabet)
What do you think? Take your pick. You'll be wearing one.
He's ignoring me again.
I'll have to get him something with lots of frills then.
What's that little dot on your cheek?
Oh, this?
It's a token of affection.
That was disgusting. You want me to show my token of affection?
Look. Will this look good on him?
Do you know what he looks like? I think something brighter might be better.
- All this fuss just over him.
- Green.
Pink?
- Let go of me.
- It's pretty. No, cute.
Actually, let's just say it looks fine.
I don't want to do long hair.
You look great with long hair.
Then why is yours shorter?
F-For me, this one works… better.
Please.
Hey. I told you, no backsies.
There's no way I'm wearing this. This is way too much.
I wasn't going to tell you this, but listen.
The other teams will be dancing and singing, too.
We need this.
Did you memorize the lines?
Of course.
Just write it down on your palms.
That won't be fair.
Of course.
That's why it's abstract.
Hey, look.
What the hell! Delete that!
You want me to? You want me to? Then call me "hyung." Say it.
(T/N: an honorific for an older male/brother)
I never call anyone that, except family.
- Delete it now!
- No. The teacher is here.
- Bonjour!
- Are you all ready for the test?
- Yes.
- No.
Still couldn't find it?
Just hang on. I know it's here somewhere.
He's definitely out of his mind.
It's fine. We just borrowed them for a day.
This is stealing, not borrowing.
I wouldn't have worn it if I'd known it was stolen.
Oh, no!
Are you scared?
Be quiet.
So, it's with the other props?
Hey. Should we beg for mercy?
Stop joking around.
What should we do? Beg? Apologize? What do you say?
Tell me.
Oh, right. Did you book the movie tickets?
[ERROR]
Do you want to watch a movie, too?
[Error]
[ERROR]
[OUT OF ORDER]
Ah, fuck.
- Lee Minho.
- Here.
- Lee Seokhun.
- Lee Handong.
- Here.
- Lee Eunbi.
[WHY DID YOU RUN OFF LIKE THAT?]
[IT'S TAKEN CARE OF, DON'T WORRY.]
[STILL MAD?]
Chu Sangwoo.
Is Chu Sangwoo here?
Hey. Is Chu Sangwoo really absent? Is something up with him?
Don't know. Maybe he's sick.
But he was in class even when he hurt his head. That's odd.
Is he really sick?
[FREELOADER 3]
[SEARCH: WEIRD BODILY SENSATIONS]
[SEARCH: ABNORMAL DESIRES]
[SEARCH: HORMONE DISORDER]
Hey, Chu Sangwoo! Are you inside?
Why didn't you come to class?
You're in there, right?
Chu Sangwoo!
I wish I could format my brain.
Hey, Chu Sangwoo!
You're in there, right?
Chu Sangwoo!
I'm sure he's in there.
Hey!
Did he faint or something?
I'm going to call 911 if you don't answer.
I'm calling 911.
What happened to you?
Stop making noise and disturbing me.
I could call the police about this.
I was worried that you might be sick.
Have you been to the doctor?
I was trying to see if you had a fever.
Mind your own business! Or I'll really call the police.
Look at you. How can I not be worried?
You weren't answering my calls. And you ignored my texts.
I never asked you to care.
I thought we were on good terms now. What's the problem?
Stop acting like we're friends.
We did that presentation together, but I still hate you.
I was just worried about you, and this is the way you talk to me?
I'm sorry I was mean to you at first.
But that only lasted three days.
And I've been trying my best to make it up to you.
I never wanted any of that.
Wow.
You have a way of pushing people away.
I still hate that I see you every day.
It must have been tough putting up with me.
All you care about is grades, anyway.
- Pathetic.
- Just get out of my sight.
Don't order me around, you bastard. You'll never see me again.
That's better.
Where's Jaeyeong?
I don't know. He's not answering my texts.
Is he up to something? Miss, can we have some soda here?
And a soju, please.
I thought you weren't coming.
Why do I have to deal with this shit when I haven't done anything?
Jaeyeong, why are you so angry?
Lettuce! Why are you eating lettuce?
Don't eat this. Damn Sangchoo!
Don't eat lettuce in front of me. No eating lettuce in front of me.
From now on, eat perilla leaves instead when I'm around. Do you get it?
But I like lettuce better.
- Are you nuts?
- Yeah, you didn't know?
Of course, I do.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
Then, are you going to finish them all?
Let me drink. I won't ask you to carry me home.
What the hell is going on with you?
Did something happen?
Don't ask.
It's all over now.
If you hate me so much, I'll keep away from you.
Chu Sangwoo.
[LOOKING FOR A DESIGNER TO COLLABORATE ON A MOBILE GAME]
Your puffy eyes are crazy! Can you even see anything?
Quit fooling around and go get me some hangover remedy.
You go get it yourself. Walk off the swelling.
We both partied hard this weekend. How come you don't have a hangover?
I never get hungover. I thought you knew that.
[DELETE 23 PHOTOS]
You just want one bottle, right?
- Thank you, kind sir.
- Sure.
- Thank you.
- Did you forget to put in the money?
- What?
Black Holic, right?
I was craving coffee myself. What a coincidence.
Take this.
You never owe anyone anything.
Here's your change.
What? Does it taste weird?
No.
- Somehow I don't like the taste.
- What?
But the ingredients haven't changed.
It tastes the same as always, like watered-down coffee.
I think your shirt is inside out.
You look totally hip. I might as well try that myself.
Here.
Why do you look so down today?
Jang Jaeyeong looking worried? That's a first.
What is it? Problems with girls?
I'm not like you.
So, you have another favor to ask?
Wow!
How could you tell so quickly?
My restaurant is opening soon, and I need handsome waiters.
Hey, do you have anybody to recommend? Or you could join us yourself.
Just serving, right?
Really? You would really do this for me?
It might be a lot of work. Will you be okay with that?
Even better then.
That'll help take my mind off things.
I can't believe you said yes!
Awesome!
This feels odd.
Why am I bothered when everything is back in place?
Did he move out?
[Jang Jaeyeong: zzang_jae_0_0]
[READY FOR FRENCH PRESENTATION]
He posted this without asking me?
[SKATEBOARDING TO BLOW AWAY THE STRESS]
This is stupid. He looks like a total bum.
How do I look? Here we go.
Idiot.
[ABOUT TO LEAVE THE STUDIO]
[I ENVY YOU. WHEN ARE YOU COMING BACK?]
[#WEEKDAYLUNCH #HANDSOME WAITERS]
[#NEWRESRAURANT #YEONSEOK-DONG]
It's in Yonseok-dong?
That's far.
What am I even doing right now?
What a waste of two hours.
Sangchoo, want to step out for a minute?
Do you have any concerns?
You look a bit off these days.
You were sighing so much in the library, too. Loudly, like that.
It's just... There is a problem I've been grappling with.
What is it? Tell me about it.
I may not be as smart as you, but I'm still pretty smart.
Well...
I eliminated the cause of the problem.
But things are not working the way they used to.
And I find myself running into errors.
Then maybe elimination was the wrong approach.
How about a rollback to the initial state and giving it another try?
- Rollback?
- Yeah.
Jaeyeong, please. We need a wingman for a triple-blind date.
Jaeyeong, just one more time.
- No. I got a new part-time job.
- Please.
Please, help us out just this once.
I said no. Out of my way.
Come on, Jaeyeong, please!
- Let go of me.
- Please come.
I didn't expect you would bring me to a place like this.
Everything looks delicious.
What do you want to have?
Anything's fine.
That's the worst kind of answer.
But it's fine. I'll pick one for you then.
Okay.
We're ready to order.
What would you like to order?
We'll have one pepperoni pizza and...
Let me give you a quick walkthrough of the menu. This is chicken, and this is...
Snowy cheese pizza is popular.
How about drinks?
Man, it's busy as hell.
Chu Sangwoo?
Did he come here because of me?
This is for table three.
I'm taking a quick break.
Of course I did well.
I'll be right back.
But the bathroom is this way...
Hey, Hyeongtak. Yeah. It's in Yeonseok-dong.
Sure. A present will be nice.
You can come now.
No. We can keep talking.
Hyung. Hang up the phone.
(T/N: Literally, called him Older Brother, he's starting to use polite/respectful speech with Jaeyeong)
I have something important to say to you.
Hyung, let's work on the game together.
Didn't you say you hated me and wanted me gone from your life?
And now you want to work with me?
For that game of yours?
Are you kidding me?
I need a skilled designer.
Like you, Hyung.
You've got to be kidding me.
You thought that if you came up to me and asked,
I would just say yes?
- That's what you wanted, Hyung.
- Stop calling me that!
Why are you calling me "hyung" all of a sudden?
- You told me to call you that.
- No.
Don't.
Forget it.
I'm not an emotionless robot like you.
So, I'm not going to work with you.
Just get back to your date.
Hey! What have you been up to?
- Sorry.
- We had a ton of work while you were gone.
The ones that sat over there are your friends, right?
No.
What? I saw the guy go after you.
Give this back to him.
What is this?
Take a look.
[CHU SANGWOO]
It's your friend's, right?
No idea. He'll come to pick it up himself.
Oh, right. That girl that was with him. Do you know her?
Bring her again some time. I'll give you guys free lunch.
I need a skilled designer!
- Like you, Hyung.
- Stop calling me that!
That sad look on his face...
You didn't come back after so long that I thought you'd run away.
The food was nice. But it was super pricey, wasn't it?
Yeah, it was a bit much.
Totally. It was more like a place to take pictures.
- There's a cafe I know over there, and—
- I need a more rational strategy.
What strategy?
Thanks for coming with me today.
I'll see you tomorrow.
What the heck? Wasn't it a date?
Damn it.
This isn't helping.
You try not to care, and then what?
Just two looks and you give up?
I'm disappointed. Jang Jaeyeong.
He probably doesn't care about you.
[ACTION GAME: VEGGIE MAN]
[CHU SANGWOO]
Why does he still have this?
Like he cares about me.
[THE ART OF UNDERSTANDING AND PERSUASION]
This is too much to learn.
Jaeyeong hyung. Please reconsider my offer.
Stop calling me that!
Why are you calling me hyung all of a sudden?
- You told me to call you that.
- No.
Don't.
You wanted me to call you hyung.
[Hello, Jaeyeong]
You think this will work?
What's the point of reading this? That won't help persuade me.
I realized that I was rude to you back then.
But you have a lot to gain from this—
Stop.
This is yours.
I'm leaving.
[ACTION GAME: VEGGIE MAN]
[CHU SANGWOO]
[I drink Black Holic]
Senior.
I really need you.
It has to be you.
So, please reconsider my offer.
I'll give it my absolute best.
Hyung.
♫ It was like time had stopped ♫
♫ I mean when I first saw you ♫
♫ I never knew there'd be a day like this ever in my life ♫
♫ And I'm glad that it happened ♫
♫ No need for any fancy words that will give you flutters ♫
Do you think we'll finish it before the semester ends?
♫ I just want you to know that I'm sincere ♫
Yes.
♫ It is now clear how I feel about you ♫
Then I'm going to redo the story and design myself because Veggie Man really sucks.
♫ I think about you, and I know it's true ♫
♫ Baby please, will you stay in my life ♫
♫ Last night in my dream ♫
[PROJECT SCHEDULE]
You have to be careful with two things.
First, keep to the deadlines.
Secondly, you have to do your best.
If you have no objections, have the new story and design ready by our next meeting.
You're kidding, right?
The next meeting is tomorrow.
We don't have much time, so we have to be quick with everything.
Really?
You have until midnight tonight. Or else we'll stick to the original.
You'll make a great boss someday.
What are these snacks? These are for grannies.
Leaving already?
I can't stay with you for long.
Why is that?
I don't want to tell you.
Oh, and one more thing.
If you're going to make physical contact, let me know in advance.
Or I'll be uncomfortable.
I'll see you at the next meeting.
Just say "tomorrow."
"Next meeting" sounds like it's further away.
Next meeting, then.
Why are you being so spineless?
You had a big fight. Why are you helping him?
He said he needed me.
He used to always glare at me,
but then he had a sad look on his face, and asked me for help.
- How could I refuse?
- How impressive.
I bet it's because he called you hyung once.
Not just once, it was four times.
You're pathetic.
[Send me the plan by midnight.]
[Meet me at the computer engineering building tomorrow.]
Do you really think it'll work?
Just the two of you?
And mid-semester, too?
Why? You think it's impossible?
You could if it's low-quality.
But judging from his personality, he probably wants perfection.
That's true.
Five minutes till midnight. You haven't sent me anything, so this is just a friendly reminder.
See, I told you.
He's already nagging you like crazy. Just don't do it.
He's not nagging. He's being thorough.
That hurt my head...
It's your turn.
Telephone?
[FREELOADER 3]
Well, maybe he has a legitimate reason.
Don't worry about that.
[WORST BOSS EVER]
What?
Really?
Hello?
It's Chu Sangwoo.
I know.
What's up?
It's midnight and I haven't received anything.
Oh, that's why you called?
It'll be ready by tomorrow.
Senior.
Yeah?
Are you playing pool?
Please respect the deadline from now on.
Okay, Mr. Tenacious.
Chu Sangwoo.
I prefer this over texting.
Why?
No reason.
I just like it better.
Good night.
You, too.
I'm going home, okay? You grab the check.
But this was your idea.
Hyung.
Hyung! Do you not hear me? Hey, Hyung!
Can't you see I'm busy?
We have an emergency.
- Do you remember these guys?
- What?
[NSTAR]
What?
That Jihye you've been talking about was this Jihye?
What? You know her? Did you see the guy she was with?
How was he? Was he handsome?
Is he tall? Tell me.
He's quite good-looking...
and has a cute smile.
What? Cuter than mine?
Take a look.
Ugh, that's disgusting. Just go home. Don't you have class tomorrow morning?
This is insane.
Aren't you going home?
[VEGGIE MAN]
[GAME DESIGN]
[INDEX]
[MARKET RESEARCH]
[DETAILS: CHARACTERS]
[RED: RED-HEADED BOY]
It looks good. Let's go with this.
Good job, really.
Is that the best you can do?
It's impossible to make something like this overnight. You little devil.
I knew you could do it.
Because it's you.
What do you like about me?
Be specific.
It's just... You're good overall.
By the way, we need to digitalize the characters.
And they'll be animated, too. So, we'll need the body parts separated.
And the format should be PNG...
- I'll e-mail you the list of requirements.
- Okay.
Also,
I'm telling you in advance.
Since you did a good job, I'll give you a pat on the head.
No way...
What was that?
- I don't want to tell you.
- That again? Come on, just tell me.
Tell me what it was.
Come on.
I came here with Sangwoo.
I didn't expect to see you here.
Same here.
I didn't know he invited you, too.
I guess you just never eat alone.
Yeah.
Everybody wants to eat with me.
- Sit here!
By the way, do you have a girlfriend, Jaeyeong?
You're really popular with the girls.
No. I don't have one.
I'm having a lot of fun these days thanks to this guy.
Sure.
Oh, right, Sangchoo! How's everything with the rollback problem we discussed before?
It's taken care of.
That's better. If you need any advice from me, I'll be glad to help.
You asked her for advice?
You never talk to me about anything.
Sangchoo! You're going to the library, right?
- Let's go together.
- No.
He has to go somewhere with me.
- Where?
You know...
You wanted me to fix the files.
I can't do that alone. I need you there.
You're coming with me.
Come with me, okay?
Don't make this so difficult. Let's just go, okay?
Where are we going? I have to go to the library—
We can't talk there! Let's go to my studio.
Your studio?
What? You don't want to?
It might be good to check your working environment
so that we can work more efficiently.
That's what I thought. Let's go.
It's always better to be efficient.
Are you a Dex fan, too?
Yes.
The quality is always good. And they're also popular.
Is that the best compliment you can give?
Whoa!
Sangchoo?
What?
Sorry about that.
That's a funny name, really. Interesting.
- Will you just stop?
- What did I do?
You can just sit over here and ignore her.
Please take out the trash.
Right now.
- Right now?
- Immediately.
Are you happy now?
You're the guest here, not the boss.
I actually find it funny that you're the one saying that now.
Was that supposed to be a joke?
Excuse me. There are other people in here, so could you be quiet?
You have really nice headphones. Put those on.
What?
There.
Who could imagine him working in my studio?
It will be tough to make the prototype by next week.
But this is our chance to work with major companies. We should at least try.
It looks like Suyeong really told a lot of people about this.
Are you sure you can keep up with your studies?
I'm feeling really well these days. I can focus better.
Is it because I'm not in class?
That's not it.
Then what?
- I don't wa—
- "Don't want to tell you."
That again? Really?
You might as well quit asking.
Why are you making a game, anyway?
With your grades, you can easily land a job without this project.
Because I like it.
I didn't know robots could "like" something.
Everybody has the same starting point in games.
They're rewarded for what they do.
I like the idea of fair and honest achievement.
Sangwoo?
Yes?
Can I pat your head...
in one minute?
- If you don't want it—
- I wouldn't hate it...
...if you just tell me in advance.
Then...
Because you like it, let's give it our best...
together.
Save.
Do not save?
No way!
I didn't save it!
What have you done?
Why don't you get some sleep?
You're making mistakes because your brain doesn't have active oxygen.
What a way to say that you're worried.
I'll sleep for half an hour.
Don't forget to wake me up. Remember.
I'll use cold water if I have to, so get some sleep.
The worst boss ever.
I thought you said we were just going to have dinner.
What's dinner without a little drink?
Thanks to someone, I had to work all night, so I'm craving some alcohol.
I tried to wake you up.
You're the one who didn't get up.
Really?
Senior,
are you asleep?
Hyung,
You're not joking with me, right?
Hyung.
You sure you didn't do anything weird to me when I was sleeping?
I'm not like you, you know.
I sent the mail, so you'll probably get a response next week.
Can I trust you on that?
Are there any other customers here?
This place is closed today. The owner is out having a good time.
Then we're the only ones here?
It's nice and quiet, isn't it?
Oh, right. I forgot you didn't drink. Then I'll take…
I'll have some more.
You're pretty good at drinking.
I thought you couldn't drink at all.
Well, you know...
I didn't feel like drinking that day.
Then, do you feel like drinking today?
Jang Jaeyeong.
Are you drunk?
Let's reverse roles.
You sure?
Fine. Try me.
Hey, Jang Jaeyeong.
Yes, Hyung?
You know, you're an idiot, right?
Of course. I know that better than anybody.
What the hell are you talking about?
You draw on people's faces. You're nuts.
Man, why did I do that
to my precious big brother? I'm such a bastard.
You always follow people around and bother them.
I was going to let it all slide…
- I was going to let it slide!
- What?
What were you going to let slide… Hyung?
You're lucky that you're good-looking.
Do you really think I'm good-looking…
Hyung?
What the hell…
Am I good-looking,
Sangwoo?
Yes.
You're really good-looking.
Warning.
I'm going to kiss you in one minute.
If you want to run away, do it now.
What are you doing?
You should be responsible for kissing me twice.
Where do you think you're going?
I'm sorry about the first time.
I won't make any excuses about it.
But right now, it's both our faults. So let's just move on.
"Both our faults?"
It was a drunken mistake!
- And we're both very drunk right now.
- It wasn't a mistake.
I'm sure you felt the same way I did.
Am I wrong?
What are you talking about?
Forget it. Does your heart beat when you see me?
- I would die if it didn't beat.
- Who said I'm talking about biology right now?
It was just a brief moment.
- If you stop getting close to me, it'll go back to normal.
- Chu Sangwoo...
So please don't give up on Veggie Man.
Are you seriously thinking about the game right now?
You stupid idiot.
How can I stop now?
You're going to leave me here like this and just focus on the damn game?
You can do it. Be reasonable and control your urges.
You're just doing this to piss me off, right?
- Then, what the hell do you want me to do? Go on a date with you?
- Is that such a problem?
We've already kissed. Who cares if we date and push it further?
Stop with this nonsense.
That damn punk.
Goddammit, Sangwoo.
Let me go!
Who the hell taught you to run away like that?
- Let me go!
- Shut up and come here.
You're so exhausting.
Don't run from me. Now give me time to think.
Wait.
Chu Sangwoo,
aren't you the type who tries to find the root of the issue?
Yeah, so?
You don't mean to say that the solution is love, right?
If you really don't know, why not try a 2-week trial?
What are you, some kind of livestreaming service?
Why? Are you afraid of subscribing?
No way.
Sangwoo.
Don't avoid it.
And don't ignore it.
Just try and feel it.
Then all that lingering confusion you feel might disappear.
Give me some time
to analyze what you just said.
[LOVELY PINK: LOVE ME, KISS ME]
Why did I ask for some time?
[FREELOADER 3]
[I REJECT YOUR OFFER]
When are you going to be done with the test?
What do you mean? I haven't even started it yet.
Not that one.
I meant the Jang Jaeyeong endurance test.
It must be killer doing things I wouldn't normally do.
What are you talking about? If you have nothing to do, help me come up with a list of questions.
I'm so hungry all of a sudden.
I'll just have lunch with Hyeongtak.
Get out of here if you aren't going to help.
What the hell…
Hey, Hyeongtak!
- Baby!
- Come here.
I'm doomed.
Our little Hyeongtak hasn't been responding to my texts.
So you weren't replying on purpose? How could you?
What? Why are you pouting? Aren't you going to give me a reason?
It seems to me the person he likes actually likes you.
- Don't tell him!
- Why are you trying to hide it?
Are you going to keep avoiding Jaeyeong forever?
What are you talking about?
Who?
No way.
- Ryu Jihye??
- She always talks about you.
Like what's your ideal type, what's your dating style,
and do you confess first. She also said that she likes someone.
It's so frustrating.
What the hell are you talking about? She doesn't like me, okay?
How do you know that? Unrequited love is always one-sided.
I know. I know it well.
Forget it. It's all over.
She said she'll confess her feelings after the exam.
"Confess?"
You won't accept her confession, right? You won't, right?
Think of our friendship—
You hang me out to dry and still call me a friend?
Forget it. Give me Jihye's number.
- Hyung?
- Now!
You have to nip things in the bud.
No matter how many times I drink it, it doesn't get any better.
Sangwoo's taste is very unique, right?
He doesn't drink that anymore.
Hey, Jihye. Do you like me?
What?
I heard you kept asking Hyeongtak questions about me.
I mean, I was just curious about you.
- Then don't confess.
- I don't like you.
But I like someone. Chu Sangwoo.
So just give up already. You know what his response will be anyways.
"I'm sorry. But I don't want to waste my time."
Thanks for the advice, but I think this is a little too much.
It seems like you and I are in similar circumstances, so why should I give up?
You're right…
Of course, I understand what you're thinking.
Chu Sangwoo has everything going for him.
He's smart, cute, pretty, and has a law-abiding spirit.
He's probably going to make a lot of money in the future.
Why is he like this all of a sudden?
But I'm not thinking of backing away from him.
If you're thinking about being around him, you have to be ready to go against me.
Does Sangchoo know that you're like this?
Of course! We go way back, you know?
But you know. Why are you acting like we're close?
Also, how dare you call him Sangchoo?
- He said I could.
- Yeah, but I don't like it.
Don't do that.
If you really have to, call him Mr. Chu.
I'll allow it. "Hey! Mr. Chu!" Like that.
What?
"Mr. Chu?"
And I was just about to start studying.
Hey, Chu Sangchoo.
Why are you acting like that? Want me to call Jaeyeong?
I said I'm fine.
How irritating…
Stop acting like a pitiful bastard,
and ask me anything. I'll tell you everything I know.
Jaeyeong's past relationships and how long they were.
Tell me everything you know.
I hate conversations about dating.
It's not that.
I just need past information in order to understand the future.
It's to measure all variables.
What the hell are you talking about?
So you want to know about Jaeyeong's love life, right?
If I have to tell you what I know,
there's Juyeong, Saebom, and Terry.
There's the senior from his department he dated when he was a freshman.
And I also fancied him myself, but I already had a girlfriend back then.
Then there's the dance major and the flight attendant.
That's all I know.
But his relationships didn't last long. And most of the exes were older than him.
Why did he break up with them?
Hey, you know how he is. He gets tired of things easily and is often impatient.
I don't think he's very serious when it comes to love.
Because you like it, let's give it our best...
together.
They also said this. He didn't show much affection and was often blunt.
It just made them feel unwanted.
Really?
Why? I guess he's not like that around you.
- I told you it's not like that.
- Okay, okay.
But I think he's changed.
An endurance test? He said that's what he's doing right now.
A guy like him? That means he's going to die soon.
Hey, you're his friend. Don't you think you're being a little too harsh?
You got pretty angry for someone who's not in a relationship with him.
Anyway, I may not know who he really is,
but he seems serious about it.
If someone does something he or she has never done before, it must be something special.
Wouldn't you agree, Chu Sangchoo?
Thank you for giving me the information,
but please don't change my name like that.
- How would you feel if I called you Choi Yoochae?
- I like it. I feel like we're close.
- Then I'll call you Miss Choi Yoochae.
- That's fine by me, Mr. Chu Sangchoo.
I have a date to go to.
You're so bad, Jaeyeong.
Talk about perfect timing!
Go inside.
I thought you asked for some time to think. Why are you here?
I thought we agreed to work on the game together.
It's hard to get a "I missed you" from you.
When are you going to start being honest with me?
Think however you want. It's your choice to be deluded.
So we first change the rendering, right?
Why? Does this make me look like a gangster?
A little.
Does it have some kind of meaning?
Not really. I just liked it.
Want me to draw you one?
No, thanks.
Hang on.
I just thought of one that would fit you.
What are you drawing?
Something you like.
You like it? You keep looking at it.
It's going to take a while to erase it.
It took me a while to draw it, so it shouldn't be easy to erase.
Senior.
Yeah?
What can we do during the two-week trial?
I'm not going to make the decision now.
You get to hold my hand.
And kissing, we already did.
The preview ends there.
How was it? Do you want to purchase the full thing?
Not really.
Hey, I could see it on your face that you wanted to buy it.
- That's not true.
- It is true.
- Did not.
- Did, too.
If someone does something he or she has never done before, it must be something special.
Should I try
for just two weeks?
"I'll announce the results from my analysis."
Was that a little too formal?
"I'll accept your proposal."
"Let's do a trial run together."
That's crazy! Is that really from Dex?
- Is it real?
-  Just a bit more.
That hurts, dude.
- That's crazy!
- I'm so jealous.
Wow, for real.
Senior, I have something to tell you.
You came, Sangwoo?
Move, dude. He needs to talk to me.
What is it?
Well...
What's going on here?
[DEX DESIGNER RECRUITMENT ANNOUNCEMENT]
[CONGRATULATIONS! YOU HAVE BEEN ADMITTED!]
How about it? What do you think about your partner?
Congratulations, Senior.
Thanks.
Are you going to go to France then?
You, didn't you have something to tell me?
It's nothing.
Should I reject the offer from Dex?
Did you really think it through?
What is there to think about?
What? Honestly, if it's not me, it can't be done.
Just focus on your work. I'll prepare for everything else.
"Prepare?"
What will you prepare for?
If there's no more coffee left, you just have to get some.
It's something I have to do.
Hey, Chu Sangwoo.
Never mind.
It's nothing.
Cheers!
- Dude, you're awesome.
- How did you do it?
Isn't he the first to do it?
Jaeyeong was always so stylish and irritating.
Let's take a few photos together before you leave, Hyung. I want to brag on my Instagram.
Calm down, people. I'm getting goosebumps.
Oh, right.
What's going to happen to that game you've been working on?
My company has been following its progress.
So I was going to give them a call.
I guess someone else will have to do it.
What is there to think about? Dex is more important.
Is that so? The reason why they were interested
in the first place was because of his design. So who knows what will happen next?
I kind of feel sorry for the other guy.
Can we visit the headquarters if we go to France?
- Drink up. We can get accepted, too.
- Really?
- We can?
- Of course!
- Yeah, I wish.
- When are we getting a job?
Not anytime soon.
- I envy him.
- How much does Dex pay?
It's robably ten times what I earn.
- Ten times?
- Yeah.
- That much?
- Yeah! It's Dex!
Man, those punks sure do talk a lot.
They're going to talk behind your back anyway.
Before, when I was with Sangchoo,
he asked about everyone you dated before.
You didn't!
So I counted all of them with my fingers.
Thankfully, there weren't more than ten.
I wonder what I did in my past life to deserve this.
I should've stopped there.
But damn… I guess I riled him up.
I said it seemed like you were going to die soon because you'd changed.
Did I do something wrong?
I don't know anymore.
He treats people like they're products, so I don't know what he's so worried about.
But you know what's funny?
You know, because of the guy who asked you about my love life,
I can't think about anything else.
I want to find him right now and ask him.
You, didn't you have something to tell me?
It's nothing.
I want to ask what it was that he wanted to tell me.
I want to ask him how he feels
about me leaving.
I guess Jaeyeong is like anyone else. You get boring when you fall in love.
I shouldn't have told you this.
Hey, isn't that normal?
People get tiresome and stale.
For the past few years, you've always been so cool.
You see… You can't be cool once you sincerely like someone.
Face it, you're not cool anymore.
What do you want me to do?
Just... Just be your usual self. Don't try to think too much about it.
Just be like the Jaeyeong I know.
Come on, stop making me cringe. I'm leaving.
Pay for me as well.
Be like the Jaeyeong you know…
It was going to get erased anyways.
Are you studying?
Come outside for a bit.
Happy birthday.
I'm the first one to congratulate you, right?
I mean, it's only been ten minutes.
How did you know?
You sent your resume when you submitted the plans.
1001.
It's like a binary number. Even your birthday's like you.
You're so weird.
I'll say something crazy while you're at it.
I'm not going to Dex.
I'm going to help you with the game.
- Senior…
- You said nobody else can do it.
You said you needed me.
- No, back then—
- I feel the same way.
I need you, too.
My heart is telling me that.
What you proposed before, I'm ready to answer.
I reject your proposal.
Please go to Dex.
- Chu Sangwoo.
- I just don't understand.
Do you really think I would be happy if you decided not to go because of me?
I'm sorry but… I'm not the stupid protagonist of a romance novel.
I see that your useless reasoning is working hard today.
Call me when the backup file is complete.
Sangwoo.
What is your heart telling you right now?
I don't care.
I just hope you succeed.
I mean it.
Thank you for the cake.
Is he telling me to leave after that?
Bastard.
Is this a curse?
[HAPPY BIRTHDAY. I'LL BUY YOU ANYTHING YOU WANT.]
[P.S. THERE WAS SOMETHING WRONG WITH THE DECORATION. I'M SERIOUS!]
What is this?
[DEX DESIGNER RECRUITMENT ANNOUNCEMENT]
[CONGRATULATIONS! YOU HAVE BEEN ADMITTED!]
[RETENIR: TO HOLD BACK]
[RETENIR: TO ENDURE, TO CONTROL ONESELF]
Long time no see, Sangwoo.
Are you preparing for your exams?
Yes.
Did you find a replacement designer?
I'll look for one after the exams.
Please don't worry about it.
I'm not worried. I'm sure you'll find someone.
Oh, I almost forgot.
The backup files.
It's also on the hard drive.
I'm relieved that I could give it to you in person.
Yes. Thank you.
Why would you drink like that?
Doesn't your throat hurt?
It's fine. I felt a bit stuffy there.
- So—
- Can I speak first?
I don't want you to get the wrong idea and give you irrelevant advice again.
Oh, okay.
Thank you.
I...
I like you a lot.
I know it's so sudden, but if not now,
I don't think I'll ever be able to tell you this.
I just wanted to confess before you rejected me.
Sorry.
How should I respond?
You don't need to. You know I can see it in your face.
To be honest, I knew from the start. I just wanted to tell you, that's all.
Before, I was worried my world would be shattered if you rejected me.
But I actually feel relieved.
Also, I think I can feel more comfortable around you now.
How about you? Do you still feel uncomfortable around me?
No.
Of course, you never know until you try it.
Good job, Jihye.
But, Sangwoo, I was a bit surprised.
About what?
"Sorry, but I don't want to waste my time."
I thought you would say that.
But you're here listening and drinking coffee with me.
I think you've changed.
I have?
Yes. I think you've improved.
They say love changes a man. I guess those romance novels weren't fake after all.
I'm too jealous to root for you on the sidelines,
but I wish you happiness, Mr. Choo
Is anyone there?
Who are you?
Are you the tenant here?
No.
I'm from the real estate agency. Do you know where the tenant is?
We came to see the place, but no one is answering the phone.
- This place?
- He wanted to move out fast.
If you see him, can you please tell him that we came to see the place?
I'm sorry. Let's go.
I'm relieved that I could give it to you in person.
Hey, Sangchoo. Jaeyeong cleared out his stuff from the studio.
Sangwoo.
What is your heart telling you right now?
- Senior…
- You said nobody else can do it.
You said you needed me.
- No, back then—
- I feel the same way.
I need you, too.
My heart is telling me that.
♫ I never knew there'd be a day like this ever in my life ♫
♫ No need for any fancy words that will give you flutters ♫
♫ I just want you to know that I'm sincere ♫
♫ It is now clear how I feel ♫
I didn't think you would be handsome.
You're in good hands.
♫ Baby please, can you stay in my life ♫
♫ I want to sit down next to you ♫
♫ And whisper love in your ear ♫
...I might put a hole in your head.
Let's go.
♫ In my dreams ♫
♫ Just you and me ♫
♫ I just want to know ♫
♫ I meant the first time ♫
♫ From the first moment I saw you ♫
Because you like it, let's give it our best...
together.
♫ The person that is in your heart ♫
♫ It's okay if it's not me ♫
♫ It doesn't matter if it takes a long time ♫
Don't avoid it.
And don't ignore it.
Just try and feel it.
Then all that lingering confusion you feel might disappear.
♫ And whisper love in your ear ♫
♫ Baby please, can you stay in my life ♫
♫ In my dreams ♫
♫ Just you and me ♫
Chu Sangwoo?
Why are you out here so late?
Why aren't you picking up your phone?
My phone?
I put it on silent.
Why did you call me so many times?
You're like an error.
Error?
Bad personality and have no sense of time. You're also capricious and irrational.
You came here to yell at me?
I don't know why I'm like this.
- Sangwoo—
- I keep telling myself to send you away.
I know it's pointless to say this to you.
I know that.
But I like you.
I like you, Hyung.
I really do.
Can I change my answer to your proposal?
No.
It's already over, so you can't.
But I'll make another proposal.
Sangwoo,
let's date.
Not a trial run.
I mean the real thing.
I was so nervous.
[6. CHARACTERS DETAILS]
I already sent it to Dex. We agreed to discuss this later.
I told them that there's a very good programmer in Korea.
I told them to hire him before another company does.
When did you prepare for all of this?
When you said you were going to find my replacement.
Then,
did you think I would let go of you that easily?
- Then, why are you leaving?
- To discuss the final terms with Dex.
If they say no, I'm going to finish "Veggie Man" before I leave.
Senior, if you miss your chance because of emotion…
Are you going to make the game by yourself? You know I prepared the outline and concept.
You're going to do all of it by yourself?
Chu Sangwoo, were you always such a corrupt CEO?
But it's Dex.
Is Dex all that? I could go to a better place if I wanted.
Don't you know your boyfriend's abilities?
My boyfriend...
I can see you like the sound of that.
Anyways, if you are going to be with me, please be mindful of three things.
Of course. This is so like you.
First...
If you don't want to get caught, lock the door.
You know I locked the door when Choi Yoochae left.
You're so smart.
credit
💞 kissasian.one 💞
♫ Copy the sun, every day is bright ♫
♫ You got me stuck. You got me stuck ♫
[Park Seo Ham]
♫ All right. All right. All right ♫
[Park Jae Chan]
[Song Ji Oh]
♫ You got me stuck. You got me stuck ♫
♫ All right ♫
[Kim No Jin]
♫ Knocking on my door ♫
♫ Unlocking my door ♫
[Kim Won Ki]
[SEMANTIC ERROR]
Did you fix all the errors?
Yes.
I thought there was an issue with the code,
but I just needed to change the output value.
Good job.
How's the preparations for the meeting going?
Let's just go to France together. Why do you want to work here in Korea?
I want to start here and expand abroad.
Okay. I guess I went against the CEO's suggestion again.
You don't believe me?
I believe you. But you're not that good with Powerpoint. Aren't you giving a presentation tomorrow?
Why? I'm good at making one now.
As if.
Why did you put this character here?
Well... Blue-colored characters instill trust in people.
I'm deleting it.
Your taste is still the same.
That's why I like you.
We won't finish today if you keep looking at me like that.
I'm just observing you.
I'm going to the bathroom. Don't touch anything.
Damn… Do you have any other templates?
What is this? Jang Jaeyeong?
[JANG JAEYEONG: MOZART]
[JANG JAEYEONG: BOARD, FULL SHOTS]
Chu Sangwoo, you pervert!
- Wait!
- What's this?
You can't look at that. You can't! Stop looking at it.
[SEMANTIC ERROR]
[CLEAR]
Okay, next.
Oh, wait.
Do it again.
Oh, really...
I'm sorry. I don't know...
I have a girlfriend.
Are you throwing it?
Go! Aren't you going?
I'm sorry.
Why? Why?
What were you looking at?
Channel Manager : taijitu_09
Thanks to kitty_100 for the segmenting.
Thanks to taijitu_09 (General Editor), and cerejacult (Chief Editor) for the editing of the English version.
Thanks to the other language moderators, and their teams.
Thanks to the viewers for watching this film on .
We hope you enjoyed it as much as we did!
This is the last take of the last shooting day!